<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/azure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/azure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Python SQLite Issue - Part 4</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2019/07/azure-devops-python-sqlite-issue-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2019/07/azure-devops-python-sqlite-issue-part-4/</guid>
      <description>Part 1: Setting up Azure Pipelines with SSH keys Part 2: Setting up Azure Pipelines (or watching it work on Python 3.6 and fail on Python 3.7) Part 3: Finishing Setup  It turns out that all the problems I was having for about ten days in trying to learn Azure Pipelines for continuous integration that I briefly touched on in Part 2 had nothing to do with me. There was a bug in Azure’s hosted images of Ubuntu used in the CI pipeline that did not include SQLite, as Python lists it as an optional module.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finishing Setup (with Dependabot and Pytest reporting) and Project Goals - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2019/06/finishing-setup-with-dependabot-and-pytest-reporting-and-project-goals-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2019/06/finishing-setup-with-dependabot-and-pytest-reporting-and-project-goals-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Part 1: Setting up Azure Pipelines with SSH keys Part 2: Setting up Azure Pipelines (or watching it work on Python 3.6 and fail on Python 3.7)  Using Dependabot to manage Python dependencies All I want is to start coding. I want to learn how to write a Pyramid app the correct way and also to start learning pytest. There&amp;rsquo;s just one more thing to do and one to tweak in Azure and then it&amp;rsquo;s time for the fun part - the actual learning and coding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Azure Pipelines - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2019/06/setting-up-azure-pipelines-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2019/06/setting-up-azure-pipelines-part-2/</guid>
      <description>In Part 1, I covered the challenges I had in setting up my SSH key with Azure Pipelines to work with my existing Github repository, which contains a new Pyramid project without any customization (yet).
Now that Azure Pipelines could build my project, I spent the last week after that trying to figure out why builds would fail on Azure with Python 3.7, not with Python 3.6 or on my local development machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning pytest using continuous integration with Azure Pipelines (or SSH key hell) - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2019/06/learning-pytest-using-continuous-integration-with-azure-pipelines-or-ssh-key-hell-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2019/06/learning-pytest-using-continuous-integration-with-azure-pipelines-or-ssh-key-hell-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I’m still on my quest to learn more Python and at the top of that list is learning pytest. I just can’t wrap my head around testing and I know my two Pyramid apps aren’t “complete” until there are tests. (I did write docs, so I have that going for me).
A couple months ago I (very easily) added continuous integration to NFLPool using Microsoft’s Azure Pipelines. I, like many other people, have been blown away by the right turn Microsoft made a few years back to embrace open source, and wanted to give Azure Pipelines a try.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
