<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Humor on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/humor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Humor on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 14:23:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/humor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bloom County 2015</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2015/11/bloom-county-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 14:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2015/11/bloom-county-2015/</guid>
      <description>Since I was a kid, I’ve been a fan of Berke Breathed’s Bloom County. Over a dozen years ago while on vacation in San Francisco, I visited a number of used bookstores and completed my Bloom County book collection. I own every Bloom County book published, including the collections and the Library series. I even bought the Humble Bundle a year or two ago to re-purchase everything digitally so I can view it on my iPad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Travel is real!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/07/time-travel-is-real/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 13:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/07/time-travel-is-real/</guid>
      <description>Time travel is real! (Or at least in London)
As seen on Twitter:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you reading NextDraft?  If not, you should be.</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/are-you-reading-nextdraft-if-not-you-should-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/are-you-reading-nextdraft-if-not-you-should-be/</guid>
      <description>Are you reading NextDraft?
If you’re not, you should be. Dave Pell curates the top 10 news items of the day, just for you, delivered straight to your inbox. Yup, it’s delivered via email, quite old school. Mr. Pell spends each morning for 3-4 hours browsing the web (no RSS reader for him!) and puts together the best stories to share and adds his own unique commentary to each of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Tecmo Brett</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/11/super-tecmo-brett/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2007 17:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/11/super-tecmo-brett/</guid>
      <description>For those of us who grew up in the 80s, Super Tecmo Bowl was the best football game ever made. There was nothing like taking Herschel Walker 90 yards, turn around, run back to your own end zone, turn around again and run 100 yards for the score. All without being tackled.
Someone took the electrifying Packer win from last Monday night against Denver, and did a mashup with Super Tecmo Bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which file extension are you?</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/02/which-file-extension-are-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2007 00:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/02/which-file-extension-are-you/</guid>
      <description>Another day, another meme. This one just happens to fit me like a glove:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy leagues for women</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2006/05/fantasy-leagues-for-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2006 13:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2006/05/fantasy-leagues-for-women/</guid>
      <description>Bill Simmons at ESPN.com might be on to something: fantasy leagues for females.
Let’s be honest: most women don’t understand males’ fascination with all things fantasy, from baseball to football. But what if they had their own? Base it on Us Weekly, spend dollars against celebrities, and let the fantasy league be played!
 Here’s the beauty of my new league. Let’s say you took a $5 flier on Denise Richards a while back, hoping she and Charlie Sheen would patch things up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do not press the red button</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/12/do-not-press-the-red-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2005 00:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/12/do-not-press-the-red-button/</guid>
      <description>If you follow this link, do NOT press the red button!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Meme</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/11/latest-meme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2005 02:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/11/latest-meme/</guid>
      <description>Latest Meme – What color should your blog be?
Figures:You’re an expressive, offbeat blogger who tends to write about anything and everything.You tend to set blogging trends, and you’re the most likely to write your own meme or survey.You are a bit distant though. Your blog is all about you – not what anyone else has to say.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Retroscope</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/10/the-retroscope/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2005 03:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/10/the-retroscope/</guid>
      <description>I am so in to the idea of building a Retroscope.
Call me crazy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avast, matey!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/09/avast-matey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2005 10:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/09/avast-matey/</guid>
      <description>Tis be Talk Like a Pirate Day matey! So get ye black pirate hat on and be the scourge of them there seas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
