<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 16:04:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Developers – We need your help!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/05/gnome-developers-we-need-your-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 16:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/05/gnome-developers-we-need-your-help/</guid>
      <description>The Marketing Hackfest kicked off a few hours ago and we need your help.
As we build the marketing plan for the GNOME 3.0 release one of the focus areas we want to talk to users about is GNOME apps.
Do you work on a GNOME application and have some cool features planned? Updated user interface? Something cool to tell GNOME users that you’d like to see included in the the GNOME 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Odds &amp; Ends</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/gnome-odds-ends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 22:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/gnome-odds-ends/</guid>
      <description>A few different things going on:
 Tomboy documentation is almost done in Mallard. I’ve really enjoyed using the Mallard syntax – so much less complex than Docbook. Every time I have to look up an element reference, I shake my head and think, “Duh! That makes so much more sense I should have figured that out!“. Nice work Shaun. I triaged some docs bugs in GNOME Bugzilla. Want to get involved with the GNOME Documentation team but don’t know where to start?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing the Marketing Team</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/07/marketing-the-marketing-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 01:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/07/marketing-the-marketing-team/</guid>
      <description>I’m a bit behind in my blogging. After getting home from GCDS, and spending the weekend with the family, and then catching up on work after a week of vacation, I’m way overdue to blog.
The GNOME Marketing BoF was the last session on Thursday at GCDS, and the last I attended before heading home Friday. Even with the room hot and sticky, everyone was engaged, and had lots of great ideas and feedback to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join the GNOME Marketing Team!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/06/join-the-gnome-marketing-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2009 04:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/06/join-the-gnome-marketing-team/</guid>
      <description>The American Marketing Association defines marketing as:
 Marketing is the activity, set of institutions, and processes for creating, communicating, delivering, and exchanging offerings that have value for customers, clients, partners, and society at large.
 I don’t think there is a question that GNOME has value for customers, clients, partners and society at large.
It’s our job to shout about that value from the rooftops, far and wide.
Right now though, we need to focus on the first part of that sentence:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
