<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>football on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/football/</link>
    <description>Recent content in football on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 16:14:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/football/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Essential Smart Football on Sale</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/02/the-essential-smart-football-on-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 16:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/02/the-essential-smart-football-on-sale/</guid>
      <description>I recently wrote about Chris B. Brown’s book, The Essential Smart Football. It’s on sale for only $0.99 this weekend as a Super Bowl special. Go get it, you won’t be disappointed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Smart About Football</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/get-smart-about-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2013 22:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/get-smart-about-football/</guid>
      <description>When NFL Network first launched, they once had a segment with Jim Fassell, the former head coach of the New York Giants. In the segment, he shows a standard offensive formation, with two tight ends, two wide receivers, a fullback and running back. He then shows the defensive formation and explains what each offensive player is supposed to do based on how the defense lines up. If a defensive cornerback plays a shallow zone (say in a standard Tampa 2 offense) the wide receiver goes long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Gameday!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/11/its-gameday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 18:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/11/its-gameday/</guid>
      <description>As a huge (American) football fan, it amuses me to no end how my children get into the excitement of game day. They know how much I love my football teams and want to know who the Packers (or Badgers) are playing each week, which other teams I want to win in the other games, and share my enthusiasm for the game. Jack’s knowledge of the players and the opposing teams is almost scary considering he is only 4 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
