<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>89.3 The Curent on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/89.3-the-curent/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 89.3 The Curent on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 14:26:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/89.3-the-curent/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>City Pages’ Oral History of 89.3 The Current</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/01/city-pages-oral-history-of-the-current/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 14:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/01/city-pages-oral-history-of-the-current/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago I was out watching football with some buddies. I was talking about my new car and how I was disappointed it didn’t have Radio Data System built in, which shows you the song name and title when listening to the radio. “Who still listens to the radio?!” he said. I replied, “I listen to The Current! We have one of the best public radio stations in the country!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Reason Why I Love The Current</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/another-reason-why-i-love-the-current/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/another-reason-why-i-love-the-current/</guid>
      <description>_Mary Lucia: Photo by Kyle Matteson under a CC-BY-NC-ND 2.0 license
_
I vividly remember the day Rev105 changed formats. My wife and I were leaving work and climbed into the car in the carpool lot. Turning on the car, Van Halen was playing. I was surprised, but I’ve always been a Van Halen fan, and dug that they were playing it. Rev105 was the most eclectic radio station I’ve ever listened to, and while I was surprised to hear Van Halen, it wasn’t out of the norm from some of the things they played.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Heard it on the Radio</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/i-heard-it-on-the-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 15:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/i-heard-it-on-the-radio/</guid>
      <description>[https://rd.io/i/QAAKK1ydOg]
I didn’t grow up in Minneapolis and missed out on the iconic radio station, WLOL. Jon Hunt reminisces about what made radio, and WLOL, great growing up for him as a kid.
I share Mr. Hunt’s enthusiasm for radio. I remember as a kid in the 80s having my boombox reading for the nightly top 10 with my finger poised over the record button so I could get a new song onto a mixtape.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
