<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Always Learning</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2021/02/always-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2021/02/always-learning/</guid>
      <description>I haven’t blogged about my progress on Silver Saucer over the last month, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean I haven&amp;rsquo;t been up to anything. I’ve continued to take the HTML, CSS, and Javascript on Coursera. I find CSS&amp;hellip; difficult. Unfortunately, I also received an email from the course instructor that Coursera will be removing this course soon, so that figures. But it&amp;rsquo;s motivation to get it done.
One of the things I tackled a few weeks ago was making an applet to sit in the macOS menu bar to control the volume of my Denon receiver located in my home theater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listening to my Record Collection Alphabetically</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2021/02/listening-to-my-record-collection-alphabetically/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2021/02/listening-to-my-record-collection-alphabetically/</guid>
      <description>I love this blog post from Discogs. I’ve often thought of doing exactly what it lays out: listen to your record collection from A to Z.
I know there are a lot of records I rarely listen to. Whether I bought them because I love the artist, because of their rarity, or just because I was taking a chance on something new, I’m sure there are records collecting dust.
I’ve done a pretty good job, especially last year in the first year of the pandemic, selling off any records I know I won’t listen to again on Discogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silver Saucer Update</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2021/01/silver-saucer-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2021/01/silver-saucer-update/</guid>
      <description>Now that I have the ability to pick a random record to play using the Discogs API, I’ve completed one of the two big features.
I’m now debating what to do next. I have a few options, all still focused on the random album feature. (I may have to cancel the “On This Day” future, but that’s a different discussion for a different time).
Learn CSS I need to learn CSS as the theme I’m using needs to be updated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Singles Part 2</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2021/01/play-singles-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2021/01/play-singles-part-2/</guid>
      <description>I was talking to my wife yesterday about my progress and she agreed that I should update my existing method used for albums to also work for singles - and that I shouldn’t just re-use that method and to avoid code duplication. It’s good to get confirmation that I’m on the right path.
But I’m stuck on how to do this.
If we look at the route to play a full album:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiring Up Play Singles</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2021/01/wiring-up-play-singles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2021/01/wiring-up-play-singles/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this year when I finished cataloging all my records in Discogs, I then put each one into a “folder”, a way for Discogs to separate different kinds of records. It’s setup by the user, so I created a folder for each type of music I have, and the number is the ID that Discogs assigned to each one:
all_folder = 0 lp_folder = 2162484 twelve_inch_folder = 2198941 ten_inch_folder = 2162486 seven_inch_folder = 2162483 cd_folder = 2162488 tape_folder = 2162487 digital_folder = 2198943 CD, Digital and Tape don’t currently have any items in them, but I hope to at least catalog my CD collection some day, but that’s a different story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Displaying the Album Information</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/12/displaying-the-album-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/12/displaying-the-album-information/</guid>
      <description>In my last blog post, I was able to pass the folder to Discogs to get a list of albums, and then pick one at random and give me information back about the album picked. That information was returned as a dictionary and now it is time to wire it up to the Chameleon template in Pyramid that will display the HTML.
Here&amp;rsquo;s an example of the JSON:
{&#39;release_title&#39;: &#39;Massey Fucking Hall&#39;, &#39;release_uri&#39;: &#39;https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iterating Through the Folder Dictionary</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/12/iterating-through-the-folder-dictionary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/12/iterating-through-the-folder-dictionary/</guid>
      <description>After taking a break and coming back to it, I finally was able to iterate through the dictionary containing the folders I’ve sorted my records in to on Discogs.
Dictionaries are a basic object in Python, but my struggles show that to be good - at anything - takes practice. And I haven’t been practicing. Thank goodness for Stack Overflow!
I embedded all kinds of print statements trying to figure out how to play with the JSON from Discogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silver Saucer Random Play Progress</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/12/silver-saucer-random-play-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/12/silver-saucer-random-play-progress/</guid>
      <description>I’ve made some good progress over the last few days on being able to pick an album at random out of a given folder and get information about it.
All of the work has focused on the back-end. Once I know I’m getting the right data out of Discogs, I’ll hook up the front-end to display it, but for now, this has been a little more complex than I expected. (It always is, isn’t it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discogs Authentication</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/12/discogs-authentication/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/12/discogs-authentication/</guid>
      <description>I was ready this morning to write a new blog post chronicling all the problems I had yesterday trying to authenticate against the Discogs API. After finding the motivation to sit down and code for a few hours, I ended the day with almost nothing done. I could access the parts of my collection that were public, but the parts that required authentication I couldn’t figure out.
I sat down with my copy of coffee this morning, re-read the Discogs API authentication documentation, and voila!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Commit Git Hooks</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/12/pre-commit-git-hooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/12/pre-commit-git-hooks/</guid>
      <description>It was a pleasant surprise recently to get an email from Michael Kennedy at Talk Python. As a previous buyer of one of the Talk Python Everything Bundle which includes a number of different Python training courses, I was eligible for the “Pro” Talk Python podcast subscription, which doesn’t included ads.
Going through the backlog, I added a bunch of episodes, and the timing of Episode 282: Pre-Commit Framework was perfect.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
