<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GNOME on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/gnome/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GNOME on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 13:23:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/gnome/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why I enjoy writing user help for GNOME</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2017/03/why-i-enjoy-writing-user-help-for-gnome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 13:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2017/03/why-i-enjoy-writing-user-help-for-gnome/</guid>
      <description>It’s been almost ten years since I started contributing to open source projects. One of the big ways I’ve contributed in the past is writing user help. Not knowing how to code then (and still really don’t know now, as hard as I try to learn Python), writing is something I enjoy and an area where I think I can make a difference.
There are a number of different places to apply a writing skill in open source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I’m going back to Linux after five years of using macOS</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2017/02/why-im-going-back-to-linux-after-five-years-of-using-macos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2017/02/why-im-going-back-to-linux-after-five-years-of-using-macos/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been a supporter of the Electronic Frontier Foundation since 2004. Their work on privacy, free expression and technology are all things I am passionate about. For the last year or so, I have become more concerned with privacy issues in technology. The rise in big data and how everything is tracking everything we do has given me significant concerns. I’ve been giving a lot of thought to which ecosystems I want to stay in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Got Started Programming</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2016/01/how-i-got-started-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2016 16:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2016/01/how-i-got-started-programming/</guid>
      <description>As I attempt to learn Python, I’m fascinated by how people are able to do this as well as how they started to learn to program.
I’m not the only one, as Ryan Gordon (aka Icculus), a well known game developer who ports many games to Linux and Mac, asked a similar question on Twitter last month.
This led to a lot of interesting tweets and Ryan created a Storify page to share them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2009 GNOME Annual Report is out!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/12/2009-gnome-annual-report-is-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 19:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/12/2009-gnome-annual-report-is-out/</guid>
      <description>From the better late than never department, the 2009 GNOME Foundation Annual Report has been released.

When Lucas first asked me to help with the annual report a year and a half ago at GUADEC in Gran Canaria, one of the goals was to try and help it come out sooner. Apparently, I had the opposite effect. I have lots of excuses, but none of them good. (Though someone did point out to me that Mozilla just released their 2009 report a few weeks ago, so I felt a bit better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Boston Summit 2010 kicks off</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/11/gnome-boston-summit-2010-kicks-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2010 15:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/11/gnome-boston-summit-2010-kicks-off/</guid>
      <description>The GNOME Boston Summit 2010 kicked off a couple hours ago. Dozens of GNOME hackers are at the Tang Center at MIT.
John (J5) Palmieri and Jon McCann helped kick off the Summit.
J5 gave an overview of what the Boston Summit is. It’s different from GUADEC which is many presentations and more formal talks. The Boston Summit is much more informal and run Barcamp style. It gives hackers a chance to hack together and get stuff done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Snowy for a Walk #4 – Meet the Cavalier King Charles Spaniel</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/10/taking-snowy-for-a-walk-4-meet-the-cavalier-king-charles-spaniel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 19:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/10/taking-snowy-for-a-walk-4-meet-the-cavalier-king-charles-spaniel/</guid>
      <description>Photo: “Untitled” by Rach
We are just two weeks away from the Boston Summit which is also the site of the upcoming Snowy Hackfest. We’re cooking up all kinds of plans for the hackfest. Our goals include:
 An HTML5 mobile client Integrating note editing into Snowy so you can edit your notes in a web browser Focus on the user interface  In other news, Snowy 0.5, “Cavalier King Charles Spaniel”, was released on Monday to coincide with the GNOME 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Summit</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/10/boston-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2010 20:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/10/boston-summit/</guid>
      <description>I’m coming to the Boston Summit for the first time. My primary purpose is to attend the Snowy Hackfest but I’m looking forward to to seeing the GNOME community, talking to Jason Clinton about GNOME 3.0 videos for GNOME 3.0 marketing and seeing my fellow board members.
Are you coming? Take a look at the GNOME Foundation blog for more.
See you in two weeks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME 2.32 Screenshots needed</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/gnome-2-32-screenshots-needed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2010 20:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/gnome-2-32-screenshots-needed/</guid>
      <description>The GNOME 2.32 release notes need your help!
If you have a GNOME 2.31.x development environment, I’m looking for 2 or 3 screenshots:
 GNOME desktop with either Nautilus (and some files and folders cut and ready to be pasted) OR 2.32 desktop with Empathy showing meta-contacts Empathy with meta-contacts Nautilus with some files or folders cut and ready to be pasted  When using the GNOME screenshot tool, you can select the entire desktop or the application with focus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Snowy for a Walk – Issue 3:  What users want</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/taking-snowy-for-a-walk-issue-3-what-users-want/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 14:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/taking-snowy-for-a-walk-issue-3-what-users-want/</guid>
      <description>We launched the sign-ups for the upcoming Tomboy Online alpha last week. As part of the sign-up process we included a brief survey asking what features those signing up were interested in and to rate them on a scale of 1 – 5, which 5 being very interested.
We asked them to rate the following features:
 Free note synchronization for Tomboy Sharing my notes so other users can read them Editing my notes from my desktop web browser Native Android app (Tomdroid) Native iOS app HTML5 offline client (for all mobile desktop browsers) Editing my notes from my mobile device (browser, native app, whatever)  Here are the results:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Snowy for a Walk – Issue 2: Alpha dog</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/taking-snowy-for-a-walk-issue-2-alpha-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:07:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/taking-snowy-for-a-walk-issue-2-alpha-dog/</guid>
      <description>(Licensed under a CC-BY 2.0 licensed by tanakawho)
Things have been relatively quiet since my last update about Snowy a couple of weeks ago. What’s been going on behind the scenes:
 Sandy triaged and assigned milestones to lots of features requests in Snowy bugzilla. Jeff hacked on Snowy to allow users to add a second OpenID provider to an existing account. Unfortunately it will have to be refactored as it works great for new users signing up but not for existing users as the form enforces that the users are unique.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
