<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Packers on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/packers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Packers on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 02:46:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/packers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Did Donald Driver Deserve Better?</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/did-donald-driver-deserve-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 02:46:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/did-donald-driver-deserve-better/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Mike Morbeckunder a Creative Commons BY-SA 2.0 license
CD Angeli, writing at CheeseheadTV, says yes, Donald Driver deserved better Saturday night, and the Packers missed an opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Gameday!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/11/its-gameday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 18:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/11/its-gameday/</guid>
      <description>As a huge (American) football fan, it amuses me to no end how my children get into the excitement of game day. They know how much I love my football teams and want to know who the Packers (or Badgers) are playing each week, which other teams I want to win in the other games, and share my enthusiasm for the game. Jack’s knowledge of the players and the opposing teams is almost scary considering he is only 4 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I have seen the future of TV</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/11/i-have-seen-the-future-of-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 21:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/11/i-have-seen-the-future-of-tv/</guid>
      <description>…and it is the ESPN app on the new Xbox 360 update that was released today.
I’ve been in the beta for the new Xbox 360 dashboard for the last month or so, and with its release today, the embargo on blogging about it has been lifted.
Since I cut the cord and got rid of cable TV last February, the one thing that has been missing is sports. I’ve been tied to whatever the four major networks want to shovel at me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a weekend of football</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/what-a-weekend-of-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2008 01:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/what-a-weekend-of-football/</guid>
      <description>What a weekend! First, the Packers take apart the Seahawks after a costly start, with a game to remember on the Frozen Tundra with the snow blowing. And then the Cowboys, the #1 seed, lose to the Giants at Texas stadium.
It’s somehow fitting that 10 years after the Packers won the Super Bowl after hosting the NFC Championship game, that they host another one.
Cross your fingers my playoff tickets come through!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
