<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vinyl on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/vinyl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vinyl on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 00:11:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/vinyl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Amazon’s Frustration Free Packaging</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/amazons-frustration-free-packaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 00:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/amazons-frustration-free-packaging/</guid>
      <description>“Certified” to be frustration free. Especially when they tape over the easy open pull tab when you’re trying to get to your new shiny vinyl record.
(It’s Volcano Choir’s first album, Unmap, if you were curious.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August Vinyl</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/10/august-vinyl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 13:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/10/august-vinyl/</guid>
      <description>Summer is the slow time for new music releases and August saw a number of great new releases, with even more coming later this fall.
Here’s some of the new releases I picked up on vinyl in August:
 Superchunk – I Hate Music: The alt rockers have been around since 1989(!) and I Hate Music is their tenth album. The album is short and sweet, clocking in at just over 37 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Mid-Life Crisis</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/09/my-mid-life-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 13:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/09/my-mid-life-crisis/</guid>
      <description>Since I turned 40 earlier this year, it was time my mid-life crisis kicked in.
Ok, that’s not true – two years ago my wife and I each set some goals, with the reward of getting a tattoo. She set a running goal (I don’t remember how many miles she had to run over the course of the year) and my goal was to get under 200 pounds. In just over 2 years, I’ve lost 40 pounds, and that was mostly stopping and starting running and working out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chvrches – The Bones of What You Believe In</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/09/chvrches-the-bones-of-what-you-believe-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 13:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/09/chvrches-the-bones-of-what-you-believe-in/</guid>
      <description>One of the albums I’ve been looking forward to the most this year is finally out today. The Bones of What You Believe In by the Glasgow band Chvrches has had singles released all summer long and the wait has been killing me. I’m only half way through my first listen on Rdio and it’s everything I wanted and more.
UPS will be delivering my vinyl copy later today and I can’t wait to give it a spin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kicking off a week about Kickstarter (and how I became a loyal Polyvinyl Records customer)</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/03/kicking-off-a-week-about-kickstarter-and-how-i-became-a-loyal-polyvinyl-records-customer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 13:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/03/kicking-off-a-week-about-kickstarter-and-how-i-became-a-loyal-polyvinyl-records-customer/</guid>
      <description>[http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/mattlunsford/help-us-save-our-office/widget/card.html]
You can’t turn around these days without hearing about Kickstarter. From movies, music, books or technology products, it seems everyone is using Kickstarter to raise funds to start a project. Over the course of the next week, I’ll be blogging about some of the projects I’ve backed, reviews, and thoughts about how Kickstarter may be used in the future.
What is Kickstarter? From their frequently asked questions:
 _Kickstarter is a funding platform for creative projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roundup 6/17/11</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/06/roundup-61711/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 14:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/06/roundup-61711/</guid>
      <description>A few links to wrap up your week:
 Minneapolis legend Bob Mould stopped by 89.3 The Current at the UBS Forum this week and read from his new autobiography, See a Little Light, and performed a few songs which you can listen to at The Current. NPR reviews his new book as well. The Foo Fighters latest album, Wasting Light, is on sale today for only $3.99. Fantastic album, recorded on analog tape, and produced by Butch Vig who produced Nirvana’s Nevermind and he’s alo the founder of Garbage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This week in music – January 4th – 11th 2011</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/this-week-in-music-january-4th-11th-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 03:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/this-week-in-music-january-4th-11th-2011/</guid>
      <description>I had an interesting week in music this last week.
I started the week taking advantage of Amazon’s $5.00 MP3 albums and picked up two celebrated releases from Minneapolis bands:
 Gayngs – Relayted: This new Minneapolis 23 member supergroup, featuring members of Bon Iver, Solid Gold and rapper P.O.S, creates a unique sound that is guaranteed to mellow you out. Perfect msuic to play in the background while cooking or reading, Gayngs will relax and soothe you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2010 Music Sales</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/2010-music-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 15:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/2010-music-sales/</guid>
      <description>” alt=”Record Store Day 2009″ width=”500″ height=”335″ /&amp;gt;Photo licensed under a CC BY-SA-2.0 license by freeloosedirt via Flickr. Picture taken outside Buffalo Records in Ventura.
Get ready to listen to the same annual cry from the music industry – “The sky is falling!” NPR’s music blog, The Record, has the details.
For the first time, all music sales, when adding CD, LP, cassette and digital – declined as a total. Digital tracks grew 1%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heard it on the Radio</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/12/heard-it-on-the-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 16:36:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/12/heard-it-on-the-radio/</guid>
      <description>Hall &amp;amp; Oates play a sold out show tonight in Minneapolis at the State Theater. I fondly remember growing up listening to my father’s lite rock station as their hits were played. With six #1 songs, it’s good to see Hall &amp;amp; Oates music celebrated for the pop genius that it is. No one is going to pretend that their songs will change the world, but they are catchy and stay with you long after you hear them – which is exactly what a good pop song should do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rolling Stone’s 25 best record stores</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/rolling-stones-25-best-record-stores/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 21:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/rolling-stones-25-best-record-stores/</guid>
      <description>Rolling Stone released their list of the 25 best record stores in the United States yesterday.
Minneapolis was well represented with Electric Fetus coming in as the sixth best record store in the U.S. and Hymie’s Vintage Records rounded out the list at twenty-five.
In July I went on a bit of a shopping spree at Electric Fetus, which is also where I spent Record Store Day 2009. There is no question that Electric Fetus has one of, if not the best, selection in the Twin Cities, though Cheapo gives them a pretty strong run for selection.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
