<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sysadmin on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/sysadmin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sysadmin on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2010 03:32:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/sysadmin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Sysadmin team update</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/02/gnome-sysadmin-team-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2010 03:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/02/gnome-sysadmin-team-update/</guid>
      <description>(This is reposted from an email earlier this evening)
Hi all, I wanted to give you a brief update on the GNOME Sysadmin team.
Last April, Owen sent out an email outlining changes to the Sysadmin team and a goal of hiring a part-time System Administrator to help coordinate the Sysadmin team. (And we’re getting closer to be the goal every day!)
Last year John Carr oversaw the team and the Sysadmin team was able to work on a number of improvements to the GNOME infrastructure, including a Bugzilla upgrade, installing a CRM system and web analytics application for the Marketing team and Plone, a CMS for a new www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Odds &amp; Ends</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/gnome-odds-ends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 22:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/gnome-odds-ends/</guid>
      <description>A few different things going on:
 Tomboy documentation is almost done in Mallard. I’ve really enjoyed using the Mallard syntax – so much less complex than Docbook. Every time I have to look up an element reference, I shake my head and think, “Duh! That makes so much more sense I should have figured that out!“. Nice work Shaun. I triaged some docs bugs in GNOME Bugzilla. Want to get involved with the GNOME Documentation team but don’t know where to start?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
