<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>polyvinyl on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/polyvinyl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in polyvinyl on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 13:46:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/polyvinyl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kicking off a week about Kickstarter (and how I became a loyal Polyvinyl Records customer)</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/03/kicking-off-a-week-about-kickstarter-and-how-i-became-a-loyal-polyvinyl-records-customer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 13:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/03/kicking-off-a-week-about-kickstarter-and-how-i-became-a-loyal-polyvinyl-records-customer/</guid>
      <description>[http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/mattlunsford/help-us-save-our-office/widget/card.html]
You can’t turn around these days without hearing about Kickstarter. From movies, music, books or technology products, it seems everyone is using Kickstarter to raise funds to start a project. Over the course of the next week, I’ll be blogging about some of the projects I’ve backed, reviews, and thoughts about how Kickstarter may be used in the future.
What is Kickstarter? From their frequently asked questions:
 _Kickstarter is a funding platform for creative projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I’m Listening to: New Music Releases 7/25</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2012/07/what-im-listening-to-new-music-releases-725/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 12:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2012/07/what-im-listening-to-new-music-releases-725/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back!
July 25th is a big day for new music. If you’re not reading the Largeheartedboy blog for new music releases, including where you can stream the new releases for free before buying (which usually comes out on Wednesdays), you should be. The list of today’s releases can be found here.
Albums I’ve purchased this week include:
Passion Pit’s Gossamer: If you’re a fan of the first album, you’ll love their second album.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>of Montreal – The Past is a Grotesque Animal 12″</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/06/of-montreal-the-past-is-a-grotesque-animal-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 18:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/06/of-montreal-the-past-is-a-grotesque-animal-12/</guid>
      <description>It’s quite fitting the day after I launched the blog that the most beautiful record I’ve purchased yet should be delivered.

of Montreal has released a 12″ album on the Polyvinyl label of The Past is a Grotesque Animal, originally recorded for Spike Jonze’s I’M HERE. It comes on light blue vinyl with a hand screen printed design by Nina / Geminitactics.
Polyvinyl is a small label out of Champaign, Illinois and features a number of indie artists that I’ve been lucky to hear on my local radio station, 89.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
