<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>records on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/records/</link>
    <description>Recent content in records on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 12:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/records/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Listening to my Record Collection Alphabetically</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2021/02/listening-to-my-record-collection-alphabetically/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2021/02/listening-to-my-record-collection-alphabetically/</guid>
      <description>I love this blog post from Discogs. I’ve often thought of doing exactly what it lays out: listen to your record collection from A to Z.
I know there are a lot of records I rarely listen to. Whether I bought them because I love the artist, because of their rarity, or just because I was taking a chance on something new, I’m sure there are records collecting dust.
I’ve done a pretty good job, especially last year in the first year of the pandemic, selling off any records I know I won’t listen to again on Discogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kicking off a week about Kickstarter (and how I became a loyal Polyvinyl Records customer)</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/03/kicking-off-a-week-about-kickstarter-and-how-i-became-a-loyal-polyvinyl-records-customer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 13:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/03/kicking-off-a-week-about-kickstarter-and-how-i-became-a-loyal-polyvinyl-records-customer/</guid>
      <description>[http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/mattlunsford/help-us-save-our-office/widget/card.html]
You can’t turn around these days without hearing about Kickstarter. From movies, music, books or technology products, it seems everyone is using Kickstarter to raise funds to start a project. Over the course of the next week, I’ll be blogging about some of the projects I’ve backed, reviews, and thoughts about how Kickstarter may be used in the future.
What is Kickstarter? From their frequently asked questions:
 _Kickstarter is a funding platform for creative projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vinyl (R)Evolution</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/06/vinyl-revolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 23:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/06/vinyl-revolution/</guid>
      <description>When I was 17 or18 years old, I wanted to be a DJ with a friend of mine. I grabbed all of my parents vinyl records, trucked them over to my friend’s house and then… we didn’t do anything. He and I eventually had a falling out and a couple years later when I inquired about getting the records back, I was dismayed to learn that his basement had flooded and they were trashed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
