<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 10:57:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Hackfest – Participating and Interacting in Communities</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/05/marketing-hackfest-participating-and-interacting-in-communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 10:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/05/marketing-hackfest-participating-and-interacting-in-communities/</guid>
      <description>A handful of us are waiting in the hotel lobby to catch a cab to the train station as the Marketing Hackfest has come to an end. Andreas has inspired me to stop procrastinating and write another blog post (hopefully it’s not the last one about the hackfest!)
Our trip here was sponsored and organized by multiple groups including ASOLIF, Technological Institute of Aragón, CESLA, the city of Zaragosa and the regional government Aragón.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Marketing Hackfest Day 1</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/05/gnome-marketing-hackfest-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 11:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/05/gnome-marketing-hackfest-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Ten brave souls have gathered in windy Zaragoza, Spain for a GNOME Marketing Hackfest to work on a marketing plan and materials for the upcoming GNOME 3.0 launch.

Day one is already done and we’re well on our way into day two and we’re getting a lot of stuff done.
Sumana has done a great job at summarizing our first day and she’s jumped in and volunteered to act as our project manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming GNOME Marketing Hackfest</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/03/upcoming-gnome-marketing-hackfest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 13:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/03/upcoming-gnome-marketing-hackfest/</guid>
      <description>Stormy was kind enough to announce our next Marketing hackfest this week while I was out sick. (I’m such a slacker, always have an excuse!)
This hackfest is all about GNOME 3.0 marketing planning, preparation and execution. GNOME 3.0 coming this fall is a huge milestone for GNOME and our role as a marketing team is to have marketing and promotion materials ready to introduce our users to what GNOME 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Odds &amp; Ends</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/gnome-odds-ends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 22:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/gnome-odds-ends/</guid>
      <description>A few different things going on:
 Tomboy documentation is almost done in Mallard. I’ve really enjoyed using the Mallard syntax – so much less complex than Docbook. Every time I have to look up an element reference, I shake my head and think, “Duh! That makes so much more sense I should have figured that out!“. Nice work Shaun. I triaged some docs bugs in GNOME Bugzilla. Want to get involved with the GNOME Documentation team but don’t know where to start?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debunking GNOME 3.0 Myths</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/debunking-gnome-3-0-myths/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 13:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/debunking-gnome-3-0-myths/</guid>
      <description>Change is hard. People go through six predictable stages as they adjust to change, which I learned at a former company. From Changecycle.com:
 People react, respond and adjust to change in a sequence of six predictable stages. The Change Cycle model identifies the thoughts, feelings and behaviors associated with each stage of change.
  Loss Doubt Discomfort Discovery Understanding Integration  With GNOME 3.0 coming out later this year, there is certain to be fear, uncertainty and doubt associated with the changes in GNOME’s user interface and applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Marketing Team Meeting Today</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/gnome-marketing-team-meeting-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 15:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/gnome-marketing-team-meeting-today/</guid>
      <description>I probably should have blogged this sooner, but the GNOME Marketing Team is having a meeting today at 22:00 GMT / 17:00 US EST.
The meeting will be held in #marketing on GIMPNet IRC. The agenda is here.
See you there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Hackfest (Part 1)</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/11/marketing-hackfest-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 13:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/11/marketing-hackfest-part-1/</guid>
      <description>I’m overdue in recapping some of my thoughts of the Marketing Hackfest. Overall, the hackfest was a success and now we begin the hard work in recapping everything we talked about, making it actionable and doing the work!
One of the best things about the hackfest, in my opinion, was the cross-section of people who attended. Each individual had different strengths and views of GNOME and it served to remind me of the different groups who use GNOME and how they use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME 3.0 talk this weekend!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/11/gnome-3-0-talk-this-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2009 15:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/11/gnome-3-0-talk-this-weekend/</guid>
      <description>My scheduled talk at the Penguins Unbound LUG in St. Paul, MN has been moved up one week to this Saturday, November 14th at 10:00 a.m. (Minnebar, the Minnesota Barcamp was recently announced for November 21st conflicting with the meeting).
I will be presenting “An Introduction to GNOME 3.0” talking about GNOME, its history, and where GNOME is going with the upcoming GNOME 3.0 release next year. If you’re in the Minneapolis / St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Marketing Hackfest &amp; Chicago GNOME Meetup</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/11/gnome-marketing-hackfest-chicago-gnome-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2009 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/11/gnome-marketing-hackfest-chicago-gnome-meetup/</guid>
      <description>We are just days away from the Marketing Hackfest in Chicago, IL. Thanks to Novell and Google’s sponsorship, nine of us are converging in Google’s Chicago office for two days.
While we’re there, we’d like to invite any Chicago GNOME users and developers to join us for a drink or bite to eat Tuesday night at 6:30 p.m. at the Rock Bottom Brewery at One West Grand Ave.
I look forward to seeing you there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Marketing Hackfest</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/10/gnome-marketing-hackfest-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 01:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/10/gnome-marketing-hackfest-2/</guid>
      <description>Three weeks from today members of the GNOME Marketing team will converge on Chicago for two days of work, brainstorming and fun.
With thanks to Google for hosting us and Novell for sponsoring us, we’ll set aside two days to work on:
 GNOME Presentation materials. We want to make it easy for for volunteers to represent GNOME at conferences, including presentations, booth materials such as banners and brochures for the GNOME Event Box and more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
