<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PC Games on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/pc-games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PC Games on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 13:14:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/pc-games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gearbox wins Homeworld Auction</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/10/gearbox-wins-homeworld-auction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 13:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/10/gearbox-wins-homeworld-auction/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Johnny Wallker under a CC-NC-ND 2.0 license I’m cleaning up some open tabs and a story of interest to me is related to the 1999 game Homeworld from Relic Entertainment.
Relic Entertainment was bought by THQ in 2004 and THQ went bankrupt this year, auctioning off a lot of old assets, Homeworld included. Six months ago TeamPixel, a small studio, started a Kickstarter campaign to gather support to try and win the rights to Homeworld from the bankruptcy court.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>links for 2009-04-05</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/04/links-for-2009-04-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 05:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/04/links-for-2009-04-05/</guid>
      <description>ul class=”delicious”li
div class=”delicious-link”a href=”http://xmlsoft.org/xmllint.html”xmllint/a/div
div class=”delicious-extended”Use xmllint to check if an XML file is valid XML/div
div class=”delicious-tags”(tags: a href=”http://delicious.com/Silwenae/docs”docs/a)/div
/li/ul</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>links for 2009-04-03</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/04/links-for-2009-04-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 05:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/04/links-for-2009-04-03/</guid>
      <description>ul class=”delicious”li
div class=”delicious-link”a href=”http://www.4thstreetfantasy.com/”Fourth Street Fantasy Convention/a/div
div class=”delicious-extended”A fantasy convention held in Minneapolis/div
div class=”delicious-tags”(tags: a href=”http://delicious.com/Silwenae/conventions”conventions/a)/div
/li/ul</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UT3 Delays</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/02/ut3-delays/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 16:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/02/ut3-delays/</guid>
      <description>Phoronix has another story up on the continued delay of the UT3 Linux client, ported by Ryan Gordon, aka icculus.
One sentenced in the story rubbed me the wrong way:
 Ryan Gordon, the one responsible for the Unreal Tournament Linux ports, has yet to provide the Linux gaming community with any status update or respond to our inquiries.
 I don’t understand how it is Ryan’s responsibility to provide an update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers, Guns &amp; Money</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/11/lawyers-guns-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 22:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/11/lawyers-guns-money/</guid>
      <description>Unreal Tournament 3 was released Monday. But the Linux client demo never appeared, and the Linux retail server and client haven’t appeared yet either.
The UT3 mailing list has also been quiet recently, but last night Icculus sent a tweet out and the news hit the mailing list soon after: UT3’s Linux bits are hung up in legal. Somewhere along the way Epic licensed some middleware that can’t be included in the Linux version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quake Wars on Foresight Linux</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/10/quake-wars-on-foresight-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2007 01:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/10/quake-wars-on-foresight-linux/</guid>
      <description>The Enemy Territory:Quake Wars Linux client was released Friday by id. The 17mb client and installer is using Icculus‘ Mojo Setup for installation. This is a welcome change from the Doom3 and Quake IV installers which required you to manually copy the .pak files from the CD or DVDs over to your hard drive. With Mojo Setup, you just run the executable file you download from id, pop the DVD in and it installs the client, Punkbuster and copies the necessary files over from the DVD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quake Wars demo out!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/10/quake-wars-demo-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 00:22:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/10/quake-wars-demo-out/</guid>
      <description>The Enemy Territory: Quake Wars demo client is out for Linux!
Fire up your bittorrent client and get it from id!
Hopefully the full version will be out soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More on the waiting game aka Quake Wars</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/10/more-on-the-waiting-game-aka-quake-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2007 14:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/10/more-on-the-waiting-game-aka-quake-wars/</guid>
      <description>I, like Phoronix, thought the Linux client was days away, but it’s weeks according to a post I saw on Linux-Gaming.net this morning:
 I’ve also been making steady progress with the Linux Client, and it’s coming along really well. We’ve been running a closed-beta test for ‘friends and family’ for a little while, and for the past couple of weeks have had a fully functional version of the demo running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waiting Game: Quake Wars</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/10/waiting-game-quake-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2007 14:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/10/waiting-game-quake-wars/</guid>
      <description>I picked up a copy of Enemy Territory: Quake Wars.
Now I’m just playing the waiting game for the Linux binary so I can play it.
I think the actual game is more fun.
But I wanted to make a statement by picking up the game during release week – it’s important to me to support commercial game companies who make Linux compatible games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say it ain&#39;t so Mr. Carmack!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/08/say-it-aint-so-mr-carmack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2007 13:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/08/say-it-aint-so-mr-carmack/</guid>
      <description>With all the good news coming out of QuakeCon this weekend (Enemy Territory, Rage, Q3 in a browser!), there was one point of disappointing news for me as a fan if id Software: id has partnered with Valve to deploy their titles on Steam.
Valve has already publicly stated it has no plans for Steam on Linux. Being former Microsoft developers, who is surprised? But id has always been a cross-platform development company and it’s disappointing to see them partner with Valve on this.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
