<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Packers on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/packers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Packers on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 02:46:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/packers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Did Donald Driver Deserve Better?</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/did-donald-driver-deserve-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 02:46:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/did-donald-driver-deserve-better/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Mike Morbeckunder a Creative Commons BY-SA 2.0 license
CD Angeli, writing at CheeseheadTV, says yes, Donald Driver deserved better Saturday night, and the Packers missed an opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Gameday!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/11/its-gameday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 18:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/11/its-gameday/</guid>
      <description>As a huge (American) football fan, it amuses me to no end how my children get into the excitement of game day. They know how much I love my football teams and want to know who the Packers (or Badgers) are playing each week, which other teams I want to win in the other games, and share my enthusiasm for the game. Jack’s knowledge of the players and the opposing teams is almost scary considering he is only 4 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emotions</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/emotions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2008 16:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/emotions/</guid>
      <description>The difference between winning and losing in the NFL is so small, but the emotions you feel afterward, winning as opposed to losing, is so great that its really not fair. When you lose, its almost like a part of you died. When you win, youve never felt more alive.
Packers General Manager Ted Thompson</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a weekend of football</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/what-a-weekend-of-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2008 01:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/what-a-weekend-of-football/</guid>
      <description>What a weekend! First, the Packers take apart the Seahawks after a costly start, with a game to remember on the Frozen Tundra with the snow blowing. And then the Cowboys, the #1 seed, lose to the Giants at Texas stadium.
It’s somehow fitting that 10 years after the Packers won the Super Bowl after hosting the NFC Championship game, that they host another one.
Cross your fingers my playoff tickets come through!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Tecmo Brett</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/11/super-tecmo-brett/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2007 17:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/11/super-tecmo-brett/</guid>
      <description>For those of us who grew up in the 80s, Super Tecmo Bowl was the best football game ever made. There was nothing like taking Herschel Walker 90 yards, turn around, run back to your own end zone, turn around again and run 100 yards for the score. All without being tackled.
Someone took the electrifying Packer win from last Monday night against Denver, and did a mashup with Super Tecmo Bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packers vs. Bears (10/7/07)</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/10/packers-vs-bears-10707/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2007 02:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/10/packers-vs-bears-10707/</guid>
      <description>I was at Lambeau Field this past Sunday to watch the Packers eventually beat themselves and lose to the Bears on national TV.
Having grown up in Wisconsin, and now living in Minnesota, the residents of Minnesota think they have a rivalry with the Bears, but any true Packer fan will tell you the only rivalry we have is with the Bears. It was my first Bears game, and the normally nice crowd was just mean when it came to the Bears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Pack Go!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/09/go-pack-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2007 01:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/09/go-pack-go/</guid>
      <description>My father and I were able to purchase season tickets again this year from a family member.
I spent this past Sunday driving to and from Lambeau Field (about 4.5 – 5 hours each way) and it was definitely worth it.
Prior to the game, there was a convention in Green Bay this past week hosting most living Congressional Medal of Honor recipients. Before the game, Brian Williams of NBC introduced, by war, those living Medal of Honor recipients who were able to attend the convention and game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2006/01/football/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2006 00:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2006/01/football/</guid>
      <description>I love this time of the year – I think I’ve watched a football game every day for the last 10 days. Even the first few bowl games with teams you’ve rarely heard of we’re quite good (and I’m still laughing at George O’Leary).
I was ecstatic to see the Badgers win decisively in Coach Alvarez’s last game. I had been walking around the last few days convinced that what the analysts said was true – Auburn’s defense was going to rip in to Wisconsin, and the Badgers had little chance to win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pack Wins!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/12/pack-wins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2005 04:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/12/pack-wins/</guid>
      <description>Driving in a car for just over 10 hours over a 24 hour period, to watch a 3.5 hour game was worth it – the Packers actually won a game this season.
While cold, it wasn’t nearly as bad as the game 3 years ago, and I only bought one hot chocolate this time.
Definitely worth it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Off to Lambeau</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/12/off-to-lambeau/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2005 16:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/12/off-to-lambeau/</guid>
      <description>I am off for a 5-6 hour drive to Green Bay to see the Packers take on the Lions. This is the latest in the season the NFL has scheduled a night game in Green Bay, the previous being Dec. 8th 2002 against the Vikings, which I was also at, and was extremely cold (I was complaining by the end of the first quarter, some Cheesehead I am).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
