<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rock the Garden on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/rock-the-garden/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rock the Garden on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 14:57:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/rock-the-garden/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Roundup 6/17/11</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/06/roundup-61711/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 14:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/06/roundup-61711/</guid>
      <description>A few links to wrap up your week:
 Minneapolis legend Bob Mould stopped by 89.3 The Current at the UBS Forum this week and read from his new autobiography, See a Little Light, and performed a few songs which you can listen to at The Current. NPR reviews his new book as well. The Foo Fighters latest album, Wasting Light, is on sale today for only $3.99. Fantastic album, recorded on analog tape, and produced by Butch Vig who produced Nirvana’s Nevermind and he’s alo the founder of Garbage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who will Rock the Garden this summer?</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/04/who-will-rock-the-garden-this-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 14:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/04/who-will-rock-the-garden-this-summer/</guid>
      <description>CC BY-NC 2.0 by Dan_h
Rock the Garden, 89.3 The Current’s annual outdoor show in partnership with the Walker Arts Center, is just under two weeks form announcing which artists will be playing to a sold out crowd in Minneapolis. The Current will be announcing the lineup on April 19th.
The boys over at Reviler take a look at who they think may be playing at Rock The Garden. With such categories as “Best Guess”, “Awesome Long Shot” and “Most Terrifying Prospect”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live concerts on The Current</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/12/live-concerts-on-the-current/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 14:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/12/live-concerts-on-the-current/</guid>
      <description>89.3 The Current, a Minnesota Public Radio station, is ending the year with a bang and broadcasting four outstanding concerts that took place in Minnesota this year.

Rock the Garden 2010 (Photo licensed under a CC NC-SA-2.0 license by Chuck Olsen via Flickr)
 Monday, December 27th: Rock The Garden. An annual show hosted by The Current at the Walker Art Center, this year’s Rock the Garden featured Retribution Gospel Choir, Sharon Jones and the Dap-Kings and MGMT.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
