<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Bird and the Bee on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/the-bird-and-the-bee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Bird and the Bee on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 15:35:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/the-bird-and-the-bee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Music of 2010</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/best-music-of-2010-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 15:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/best-music-of-2010-2/</guid>
      <description>2010 has gone and now it’s time to share some of my favorite music of the year. Everyone has a top 10 list, so I thought I’d try something different. Well, that, and I can’t seem to whittle my list down to ten.
2010 was a great year for music. For the last few years music executives have been crying that the sky has falling as music sales decline. What they need to remember is that quality beats quantity – when they stop focusing on hit makers and on quality music and artists who will last, the sales will be there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heard it on the Radio</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/12/heard-it-on-the-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 16:36:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/12/heard-it-on-the-radio/</guid>
      <description>Hall &amp;amp; Oates play a sold out show tonight in Minneapolis at the State Theater. I fondly remember growing up listening to my father’s lite rock station as their hits were played. With six #1 songs, it’s good to see Hall &amp;amp; Oates music celebrated for the pop genius that it is. No one is going to pretend that their songs will change the world, but they are catchy and stay with you long after you hear them – which is exactly what a good pop song should do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
