<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GUADEC on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/guadec/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GUADEC on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 15:43:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/guadec/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Journal Issue 21 is out!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/gnome-journal-issue-21-is-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 15:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/gnome-journal-issue-21-is-out/</guid>
      <description>The GNOME Journal team has released the latest issue, featuring five brand new articles.
We have three articles based on talks and experiences at GUADEC 2010 in The Hague and two interviews.
 Writing simple, real-time games by Chris Lord Should I get involved? by William Carlson (aka Williamfromtexas) Behind the Scenes with Joanmarie Diggs Grilo: Integrating multimedia content in your application by Iago Toral GNOME Advisory Board interview with Bradley Kuhn by Stormy Peters  What are you waiting for?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GUADEC Closing Ceremony today at 17:15 in Paris</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/07/guadec-closing-ceremony-today-at-1715-in-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 13:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/07/guadec-closing-ceremony-today-at-1715-in-paris/</guid>
      <description>Don’t forget to come to the Paris room at 17:15 for the closing ceremony at GUADEC.
Why? You’ll want to find out where the Desktop Summit next year is!
See you there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At GUADEC</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/07/at-guadec/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 15:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/07/at-guadec/</guid>
      <description>I’m a bad blogger – for the last two weeks I’ve been telling myself to write a nice “I’m going to GUADEC” post on my blog, but here I am already at GUADEC with only excuses why I didn’t. I blame Vincent!
But I’m here at GUADEC and we had a good Board meeting – it was good to see some faces I haven’t seen in a while and meet new ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Zazzle Store Sale</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/07/gnome-zazzle-store-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 00:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/07/gnome-zazzle-store-sale/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow is the last day to save 17.76% at the GNOME Zazzle store. Zazzle is having a sale to celebrate Independence Day here in America. GUADEC is coming so now is a great time to place your order and have some cool gear to show off to all your GNOME friends in The Hague!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing the Marketing Team</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/07/marketing-the-marketing-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 01:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/07/marketing-the-marketing-team/</guid>
      <description>I’m a bit behind in my blogging. After getting home from GCDS, and spending the weekend with the family, and then catching up on work after a week of vacation, I’m way overdue to blog.
The GNOME Marketing BoF was the last session on Thursday at GCDS, and the last I attended before heading home Friday. Even with the room hot and sticky, everyone was engaged, and had lots of great ideas and feedback to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gran Canaria Part II</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/07/gran-canaria-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 14:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/07/gran-canaria-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>I continue to have a great time here at the Gran Canaria Desktop Summit. I keep putting off blogging as I’m just overwhelmed with everything going through my head, and trying to make a succinct blog post has been a challenge.
One of the best parts, especially as it’s my first GUADEC, is how welcoming everyone is. I think I’ve had lunch or dinner with a different group of people every meal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I should be packing</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/07/i-should-be-packing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 04:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/07/i-should-be-packing/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow night at this time, thanks to the generosity of the GNOME Foundation which is sponsoring my travel, I will be on a flight (hopefully asleep) crossing the Atlantic. I’m heading to Europe for the first time to attend the Gran Canaria Desktop Summit. (My wife is fairly annoyed my first trip to Europe does not include her, but that’s another story).
A few of us from the GNOME Journal team will be there – if you have an idea for an article, interview, or a cool app to show off, please look me up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GUADEC!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/05/guadec/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2009 14:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/05/guadec/</guid>
      <description>I’m going to GUADEC this year!
In all my travels, I’ve visited almost all 50 states in the U.S., but I’ve never travelled internationally. Now in the span of 30 days, I’ll be visiting both Canada and Europe – and both are related for GNOME events. And I’d like to say a big thank you to GNOME for helping subsidize my travel to both events.
The initial GUADEC schedule was posted this morning, and I’m excited (and nervous) that Stormy’s and my Birds of a Feather session on GNOME marketing was accepted!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
