<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stores on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/stores/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stores on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 14:57:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/stores/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Roundup 6/17/11</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/06/roundup-61711/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 14:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/06/roundup-61711/</guid>
      <description>A few links to wrap up your week:
 Minneapolis legend Bob Mould stopped by 89.3 The Current at the UBS Forum this week and read from his new autobiography, See a Little Light, and performed a few songs which you can listen to at The Current. NPR reviews his new book as well. The Foo Fighters latest album, Wasting Light, is on sale today for only $3.99. Fantastic album, recorded on analog tape, and produced by Butch Vig who produced Nirvana’s Nevermind and he’s alo the founder of Garbage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which is better – support the artists or the indie stores?</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/which-is-better-support-the-artists-or-the-indie-stores/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 17:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/which-is-better-support-the-artists-or-the-indie-stores/</guid>
      <description>Since I started collecting vinyl records again last year, I’ve pre-ordered a number of new albums directly from the artist’s website. I’ve often advocated for what Techdirt calls “Cwf + Rtb” – Connect with Fans + Reason to buy = $$$.
As the music industry sees declining sales, if you can connect with your fans on an individual level and give them a reason to buy, you will see revenue. This works in music and, as Cory Doctorow is proving, works in the book industry as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2010 Music Sales</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/2010-music-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 15:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/2010-music-sales/</guid>
      <description>” alt=”Record Store Day 2009″ width=”500″ height=”335″ /&amp;gt;Photo licensed under a CC BY-SA-2.0 license by freeloosedirt via Flickr. Picture taken outside Buffalo Records in Ventura.
Get ready to listen to the same annual cry from the music industry – “The sky is falling!” NPR’s music blog, The Record, has the details.
For the first time, all music sales, when adding CD, LP, cassette and digital – declined as a total. Digital tracks grew 1%.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
