<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mashups on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/mashups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mashups on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 19:47:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/mashups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best of Bootie 2013 Released!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/best-of-bootie-2013-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 19:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/best-of-bootie-2013-released/</guid>
      <description>Best of Bootie 2013 is out! And just in time for Christmas, too!
Featuring 22 of the year’s best mashups from some of the best DJs currently in the business, Best of Bootie 2013 is available as one big MP3 file or 22 tracks in one convenient zip file. Curated by A Plus D, aka DJs Adrian &amp;amp; Mysterious D, founders of Bootie, they didn’t just stop with their 22 favorite mashups – there are also 10 bonus mashups available for download, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best of Bootie 2010</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/12/best-of-bootie-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 16:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/12/best-of-bootie-2010/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to Glee, mainstream America was introduced to the term mashup in 2010. But to some of us, we’ve been listening to mashups for years. Bootie, started in 2003 by DJs Adrian and Mysterious D, hosts monthly dance parties featuring mashups. Starting in 2005, they started publishing the year’s best mashups on their website. I’m not into pop music and Bootie is what introduces me to what’s been popular in the past year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best of Bootie 2007</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/best-of-bootie-2007/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2008 13:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/best-of-bootie-2007/</guid>
      <description>It’s time for my annual post telling you to go download the Best of Bootie. The 2007 compilation features 21 of the year’s best mashups from the usual suspects such as A + D, Party Ben and more.
My favorites this year (so far, after 3 listens):
  The Illuminoids with Donita Sparks – Pretend We’re Alala (L7 vs. CSS) – Los Angeles    team9 – Britney – Dead Or Alive?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
