<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NFLPool on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/nflpool/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NFLPool on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/nflpool/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning How to Test in Python and Pyramid</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2018/09/learning-how-to-test-in-python-and-pyramid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2018/09/learning-how-to-test-in-python-and-pyramid/</guid>
      <description>tl;dr: I don’t get testing, but thanks to Talk Python I’m starting to put it together. If you’ve taken both the Python for Entrepreneurs course and the Building Data Driven Web Apps with Pyramid this might help you write tests using the Python for Entrepreneurs code. And if you’ve taken courses at Talk Python, take advantage of the office hours!
I don’t get testing in Python at all. I don’t have a computer science degree and Python is a hobby for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There is No Offseason</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2018/08/there-is-no-offseason/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2018/08/there-is-no-offseason/</guid>
      <description>Alternative title: There is No Offseason (or writing my Python apps never ends and that&amp;rsquo;s ok) The blogging might slow down some, but the coding never stops. Ok, well maybe a little. After creating and launching MLBPool2 this past spring, I took a small break and then back at it for the upcoming season of NFLPool.
I have two big goals for NFLPool before the 2018 season starts:
 Fix the time / timezone issue where a player tried to submit his picks before the first game of the season started to, but was denied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Password Validation in NFLPool and MLBPool2</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2018/04/password-validation-in-nflpool-and-mlbpool2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2018/04/password-validation-in-nflpool-and-mlbpool2/</guid>
      <description>When I first learned to work with Pyramid thanks to the Talk Python course Python for Entrepreneurs, I used the account registration system directly from the course for NFLPool. When I wrote MLBPool2, I augmented it to require the user to use a much stronger password than the course taught. (You can see the original code from NFLPool here).
In MLBPool2, I required the user to use a password between 8 and 24 characters and it must have at least one lowercase letter, at least one upper case letter, a number, and a symbol:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFLPool - The Work Continues</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2018/04/nflpool-the-work-continues/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2018/04/nflpool-the-work-continues/</guid>
      <description>For once in my life, I’m not procrastinating. With the NFL season just over four and a half months away, I’ve already started on working to update NFLPool.
I’m really enjoying working with Python and don’t want to let the few things I’ve learned get rusty. This includes back porting a number of updates from MLBPool2.
I&amp;rsquo;ve updated the Standings page to display all seasons played (before it defaulted to just the current season).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MLBPool2 – Letting a Player Change their Picks</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2018/03/mlbpool2-letting-a-player-change-their-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2018/03/mlbpool2-letting-a-player-change-their-picks/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been blogging a little bit about MLBPool2 the last couple of weeks and now the last three months of work is complete.
I already touched on two of the biggest differences between NFLPool and MLBPool2 (the time service using Pendulum and using MySQL / MariaDB instead of SQLite).
The biggest difference between NFLPool and MLBPool2 though is players have the ability to change their picks. At the All-Star Break, MLBPool2 players can change up to 14 of their 37 picks, but those changes are only worth half points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where I get stats for MLBPool and NFLPool: MySportsFeeds (and it’s awesome)</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2018/03/mysportsfeeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 13:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2018/03/mysportsfeeds/</guid>
      <description>A few years ago I started to look into how I could build apps to manage MLBPool and NFLPool. The key would be how to integrate all of the team and player statistics and where to get that data. I was floored when I saw the pricing of how much companies charge to provide those stats – it was hundreds to thousands of dollars per month to get access to baseball or football stats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MLBPool2 &amp; MySQL / MariaDB</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2018/03/mlbpool2-mysql-mariadb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 17:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2018/03/mlbpool2-mysql-mariadb/</guid>
      <description>When I wrote yesterday introducing MLBPool2, I buried the lede. One of the biggest changes between NFLPool and MLBPool2 is the fact I’m now using MariaDB and MySQL as the backend instead of SQLite, which NFLPool uses. (I did look at PostgreSQL since so many Python developers seem to prefer it, but I’ve never been able to get a PostgreSQL server up and running on Linux or Mac. My sysadmin skills are nonexistent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing MLBPool2</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2018/03/introducing-mlbpool2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 14:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2018/03/introducing-mlbpool2/</guid>
      <description>After learning Python and creating NFLPool, it was time for another project. This time it was building the site for MLBPool2, which inspired NFLPool. MLBPool was the brain child of former commissioner Jason Theros who created the league and rules. Sadly, MLBPool came to an end after the 2011 season. The original site was written in ASP and none of the code was available and for the last few years after my friend resurrected the league he did almost everything by hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFLPool 2017 Recap</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2018/01/nflpool-2017-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 13:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2018/01/nflpool-2017-recap/</guid>
      <description>The NFLPool 2017 season wrapped up a month ago. The application performed admirably. Every week I logged in, downloaded the weekly statistics from MySportsFeeds, and the scoring calculations updated and posted on the standings page. I emailed the players every other week with the update and link to the standings (and the reminder that the team standings points would not be final until the end of the season due to MySportsFeeds shows division standings doesn’t account for the correct tiebreakers).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFLPool: a (kind of) Post Mortem</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2017/10/nflpool-a-kind-of-post-mortem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 13:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2017/10/nflpool-a-kind-of-post-mortem/</guid>
      <description>I’m now four weeks into NFLPool being live. The week leading up to and after the launch of NFLPool for NFL week 1 was kind of a blur. I wish I had taken better notes or wrote down everything that happened, but now being a month into it, here are some random thoughts.
Submitting Picks Somewhere in my code, I screwed up the function to disallow making picks. The code should have refused to let a user make picks after 7pm CST on the Thursday kickoff of the first game, about twenty minutes before the game starts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
