<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Football on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/football/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Football on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 16:14:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/football/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Essential Smart Football on Sale</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/02/the-essential-smart-football-on-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 16:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/02/the-essential-smart-football-on-sale/</guid>
      <description>I recently wrote about Chris B. Brown’s book, The Essential Smart Football. It’s on sale for only $0.99 this weekend as a Super Bowl special. Go get it, you won’t be disappointed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Smart About Football</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/get-smart-about-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2013 22:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/get-smart-about-football/</guid>
      <description>When NFL Network first launched, they once had a segment with Jim Fassell, the former head coach of the New York Giants. In the segment, he shows a standard offensive formation, with two tight ends, two wide receivers, a fullback and running back. He then shows the defensive formation and explains what each offensive player is supposed to do based on how the defense lines up. If a defensive cornerback plays a shallow zone (say in a standard Tampa 2 offense) the wide receiver goes long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I have seen the future of TV</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/11/i-have-seen-the-future-of-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 21:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/11/i-have-seen-the-future-of-tv/</guid>
      <description>…and it is the ESPN app on the new Xbox 360 update that was released today.
I’ve been in the beta for the new Xbox 360 dashboard for the last month or so, and with its release today, the embargo on blogging about it has been lifted.
Since I cut the cord and got rid of cable TV last February, the one thing that has been missing is sports. I’ve been tied to whatever the four major networks want to shovel at me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a weekend of football</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/what-a-weekend-of-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2008 01:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/what-a-weekend-of-football/</guid>
      <description>What a weekend! First, the Packers take apart the Seahawks after a costly start, with a game to remember on the Frozen Tundra with the snow blowing. And then the Cowboys, the #1 seed, lose to the Giants at Texas stadium.
It’s somehow fitting that 10 years after the Packers won the Super Bowl after hosting the NFC Championship game, that they host another one.
Cross your fingers my playoff tickets come through!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packers vs. Bears (10/7/07)</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/10/packers-vs-bears-10707/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2007 02:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/10/packers-vs-bears-10707/</guid>
      <description>I was at Lambeau Field this past Sunday to watch the Packers eventually beat themselves and lose to the Bears on national TV.
Having grown up in Wisconsin, and now living in Minnesota, the residents of Minnesota think they have a rivalry with the Bears, but any true Packer fan will tell you the only rivalry we have is with the Bears. It was my first Bears game, and the normally nice crowd was just mean when it came to the Bears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Bloody Thursday</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2006/03/welcome-to-bloody-thursday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2006 12:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2006/03/welcome-to-bloody-thursday/</guid>
      <description>If you’re an NFL fan, Len Pasquarelli of ESPN.com has a must read article on what they’re calling today: Bloody Thursday. His follow-up article on what will go down to today is just as good.
With the Collective Bargaining Agreement between the Player’s Union and Owners set to expire tomorrow, teams must get under the salary cap – a cap number they still don’t know. Free Agency starts tomorrow, and 2007 will be an uncapped year, so teams will be reluctant to sign anyone, especially as they can only pro-rate contracts over 4 years instead of the typical 7, which drives a player’s salary cap number through the roof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playoff thoughts</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2006/01/playoff-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2006 03:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2006/01/playoff-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>I’m not sure why, but I was happy to see the Steelers win this afternoon.
The Colts have a coach who is well respected, with a rep he can’t win the big one, but who is supposed to be one of the nicest coaches you’ll ever meet. They have one of the best, if not the best, quarterback in the league. And yet I was rooting against them.
There’s something about Bill Cowher that makes me cheer for the man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2006/01/football/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2006 00:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2006/01/football/</guid>
      <description>I love this time of the year – I think I’ve watched a football game every day for the last 10 days. Even the first few bowl games with teams you’ve rarely heard of we’re quite good (and I’m still laughing at George O’Leary).
I was ecstatic to see the Badgers win decisively in Coach Alvarez’s last game. I had been walking around the last few days convinced that what the analysts said was true – Auburn’s defense was going to rip in to Wisconsin, and the Badgers had little chance to win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pack Wins!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/12/pack-wins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2005 04:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/12/pack-wins/</guid>
      <description>Driving in a car for just over 10 hours over a 24 hour period, to watch a 3.5 hour game was worth it – the Packers actually won a game this season.
While cold, it wasn’t nearly as bad as the game 3 years ago, and I only bought one hot chocolate this time.
Definitely worth it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Off to Lambeau</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/12/off-to-lambeau/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2005 16:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/12/off-to-lambeau/</guid>
      <description>I am off for a 5-6 hour drive to Green Bay to see the Packers take on the Lions. This is the latest in the season the NFL has scheduled a night game in Green Bay, the previous being Dec. 8th 2002 against the Vikings, which I was also at, and was extremely cold (I was complaining by the end of the first quarter, some Cheesehead I am).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
