<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Used on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/used/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Used on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 03:52:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/used/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This week in music – January 4th – 11th 2011</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/this-week-in-music-january-4th-11th-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 03:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/this-week-in-music-january-4th-11th-2011/</guid>
      <description>I had an interesting week in music this last week.
I started the week taking advantage of Amazon’s $5.00 MP3 albums and picked up two celebrated releases from Minneapolis bands:
 Gayngs – Relayted: This new Minneapolis 23 member supergroup, featuring members of Bon Iver, Solid Gold and rapper P.O.S, creates a unique sound that is guaranteed to mellow you out. Perfect msuic to play in the background while cooking or reading, Gayngs will relax and soothe you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rolling Stone’s 25 best record stores</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/rolling-stones-25-best-record-stores/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 21:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/rolling-stones-25-best-record-stores/</guid>
      <description>Rolling Stone released their list of the 25 best record stores in the United States yesterday.
Minneapolis was well represented with Electric Fetus coming in as the sixth best record store in the U.S. and Hymie’s Vintage Records rounded out the list at twenty-five.
In July I went on a bit of a shopping spree at Electric Fetus, which is also where I spent Record Store Day 2009. There is no question that Electric Fetus has one of, if not the best, selection in the Twin Cities, though Cheapo gives them a pretty strong run for selection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prince: Purple Rain</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/07/prince-purple-rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 23:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/07/prince-purple-rain/</guid>
      <description>Prince’s Purple Rain will also hold a special place for me as it was the first album I ever purchased. Oh, I had owned some 45s up until that point, but growing up I spent my summers at my grandparents house, and I remember as an eleven year old walking from their house to the local record store and buying it.
I think my grandparents, and my parents for that matter, might not have let an eleven year old buy the album considering some of the lyrics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
