<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pytest on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/pytest/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pytest on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/pytest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Silver Saucer</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/07/introducing-silver-saucer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/07/introducing-silver-saucer/</guid>
      <description>I’ve started my next Python project: Silver Saucer, which will be hosted at silversaucer.com. I originally bought the domain about ten years ago when I was thinking of going into business for myself, which never happened and I hung onto the domain name because I liked it. It was inspired by Neil Gaiman’s poem, The Day The Saucers Came, which I also have a framed art print of:
 The Day the Saucers Came   Once upon a time, I was also a big fan of The X-Files, so it seems fitting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning pytest using continuous integration with Azure Pipelines (or SSH key hell) - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2019/06/learning-pytest-using-continuous-integration-with-azure-pipelines-or-ssh-key-hell-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2019/06/learning-pytest-using-continuous-integration-with-azure-pipelines-or-ssh-key-hell-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I’m still on my quest to learn more Python and at the top of that list is learning pytest. I just can’t wrap my head around testing and I know my two Pyramid apps aren’t “complete” until there are tests. (I did write docs, so I have that going for me).
A couple months ago I (very easily) added continuous integration to NFLPool using Microsoft’s Azure Pipelines. I, like many other people, have been blown away by the right turn Microsoft made a few years back to embrace open source, and wanted to give Azure Pipelines a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MLBPool2 is live!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2018/03/mlbpool2-is-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 01:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2018/03/mlbpool2-is-live/</guid>
      <description>I deployed MLBPool2 on Monday. I had a flurry of activity over the weekend to fix a scoring bug. No matter how hard I tried, I couldn’t get MLBPool2 to match the 2017 results that were done by hand. I learned that I don’t have the patience to hand enter the picks for 16 players and then all of their All-Star Break changes. I did it three times and every time I would catch a mistake that I made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s next for NFLPool</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2017/10/whats-next-for-nflpool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 12:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2017/10/whats-next-for-nflpool/</guid>
      <description>NFLPool has been up for six weeks and everything is working great. I’ve been updating the standings every Tuesday without any issues. I’ve taken the last month to catch my breath after my massive coding spree to get it launched and I’ve been thinking about what’s next. I have a few options:
 Add some tests (all Python projects should have tests written, right?) Adding documentation in reStructured Text to NFLPool Re-visit some of the Python trainings now that I have a basic grasp of Python and learn some more “advanced” concepts (generators, list comprehensions, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
