<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 14:23:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bloom County 2015</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2015/11/bloom-county-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 14:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2015/11/bloom-county-2015/</guid>
      <description>Since I was a kid, I’ve been a fan of Berke Breathed’s Bloom County. Over a dozen years ago while on vacation in San Francisco, I visited a number of used bookstores and completed my Bloom County book collection. I own every Bloom County book published, including the collections and the Library series. I even bought the Humble Bundle a year or two ago to re-purchase everything digitally so I can view it on my iPad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Larry Elmore: The Complete Elmore Artbook</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/larry-elmore-the-complete-elmore-artbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 16:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/larry-elmore-the-complete-elmore-artbook/</guid>
      <description>If you played Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons in the 80s, read the Dragonlance novels published by TSR or played Everquest, chances are you have seen artwork by Larry Elmore.
Just about a year ago Mr. Elmore launched a Kickstarter to publish most of his painted art from the last 40 years, and it was successfully funded on New Year’s Eve of 2012.
Imagine my surprise yesterday when the US Postal Service rang my doorbell and delivered my Kickstarter package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The “Last” Science Fiction / Fantasy Meme</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/10/the-last-science-fiction-fantasy-meme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 13:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/10/the-last-science-fiction-fantasy-meme/</guid>
      <description>SF Signal, the most recent Hugo award winning fanzine, posted a meme on Saturday with a “last” theme. Here we go:
 The last sf/f book I finished reading: Shift Omnibus by Hugh Howey The last sf/f book I did NOT finish: Perdido Street Station by China Miéville (I loved The City &amp;amp; the City but just could not finish this one. It’s very rare for me to not finish a book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Godspeed Mr. Banks – 1954-2013</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/06/godspeed-mr-banks-1954-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 06:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/06/godspeed-mr-banks-1954-2013/</guid>
      <description>
Iain Banks, one of my favorite authors, was diagnosed with cancer this past April, which I previously wrote about. He passed away yesterday at the age of 59.
Charlie Stross and Neil Gaiman each share their thoughts on his passing. Their words far surpass anything I could write.
Godspeed Mr. Banks.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iain Banks</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/04/iain-banks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 14:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/04/iain-banks/</guid>
      <description>I was sad to learn this morning that Iain Banks shared that he has terminal cancer and probably only less than a year to live. I first saw the news via Charles Stross’ Twitter account and a number of other people have shared the news this morning.

The first book I read of Iain Bainks was his Culture novel, Use of Weapons. He writes his science fiction books as Iain M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Moore &amp; the Guy Fawkes Mask</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/11/alan-moore-the-guy-fawkes-mask/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 15:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/11/alan-moore-the-guy-fawkes-mask/</guid>
      <description>Alan Moore talk to The Guardian about V for Vendetta and the use of the Guy Fawkes mask he created for V for Vendetta and its use by Occupy.
 It is an irony noted with relish by critics of the protests – one also glumly acknowledged by many of the protesters – that the purchase of so many _Vendetta _masks has become a lucrative little side-earner for Time Warner, the media company that owns the rights to Moore’s creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready Player One is the best book you’re not reading</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/08/ready-player-one-is-the-best-book-youre-not-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 13:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/08/ready-player-one-is-the-best-book-youre-not-reading/</guid>
      <description>If you grew up in the 80s like me, especially as a teenager, Ready Player One is a book for you.
For fans of retro arcade games, 80s music and movies, MMOs, cyberpunk, roleplaying and early computers like the TRS-80, it weaves them all into a story that will keep you on the edge of your seat.
I can’t do it justice, so read the summary here. And then buy it and read it, you won’t be disappointed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eBook Readers &amp; the Publishing Industry</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/12/ebook-readers-the-publishing-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 15:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/12/ebook-readers-the-publishing-industry/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been wanting an eReader for a while. When the Kindle first launched, I was in awe. I quickly sat down and calculated the number of books I buy in a year and compared that against the cost of a Kindle and the savings of buying an e-book for $10 vs. the hardcover price. Let’s just say there wasn’t much of a savings. I finally got to touch a Kindle at GUADEC this summer, and my mind was made up that I had to have an eReader in the near future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gregory Mcdonald, RIP</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/09/gregory-mcdonald-rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 13:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/09/gregory-mcdonald-rip/</guid>
      <description>Gregory Mcdonald, most famous for being the author of the Fletch series, has died at age 71 from cancer.
I’m not a big mystery reader, but due to Kevin Smith‘s praise for McDonald’s dialogue in his novels, I picked up one or two of his books, and then quickly bought them all a number of years ago.
You thought the Fletch movies (well, at least the first one) were funny? Each and every one of these books will have you chuckling and laughing out loud at some point, and the mysteries weren’t half bad either.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philip K. Dick</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/05/philip-k-dick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2007 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/05/philip-k-dick/</guid>
      <description>I mentioned a few weeks ago a link from Total Dick-Head, a blog dedicated to all things Philip K. Dick. Today’s post covers the new Library of America release of four of Dick’s most original novels that is released today in one hardcover edition. The novels are:
 The Man in the High Castle The Three Stigmata of Palmer Eldritch Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep? Ubik  The Library of America’s mission is to _“preserve the nation’s cultural heritage by publishing America’s best and most significant writing in authoritative editions is as strong as ever.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
