<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The National on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/the-national/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The National on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 22:17:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/the-national/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Favorite Albums of 2013</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/01/favorite-albums-of-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 22:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/01/favorite-albums-of-2013/</guid>
      <description>[http://www.flickr.com/photos/silwenae/11061236153/in/set-72157638067918784/player/]
With 2013 now in the books, I’d like to share some of my favorite albums of 2013. After Polica dropped their debut album digitally on December 20th, 2011, I’ve learned to wait until the year is over to share my favorite albums – don’t want to miss one!
These might not be the critic’s choices, but these are albums I like, and almost all of them I’ve bought on vinyl this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2010 Music Sales</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/2010-music-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 15:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/2010-music-sales/</guid>
      <description>” alt=”Record Store Day 2009″ width=”500″ height=”335″ /&amp;gt;Photo licensed under a CC BY-SA-2.0 license by freeloosedirt via Flickr. Picture taken outside Buffalo Records in Ventura.
Get ready to listen to the same annual cry from the music industry – “The sky is falling!” NPR’s music blog, The Record, has the details.
For the first time, all music sales, when adding CD, LP, cassette and digital – declined as a total. Digital tracks grew 1%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Music of 2010</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/best-music-of-2010-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 15:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/01/best-music-of-2010-2/</guid>
      <description>2010 has gone and now it’s time to share some of my favorite music of the year. Everyone has a top 10 list, so I thought I’d try something different. Well, that, and I can’t seem to whittle my list down to ten.
2010 was a great year for music. For the last few years music executives have been crying that the sky has falling as music sales decline. What they need to remember is that quality beats quantity – when they stop focusing on hit makers and on quality music and artists who will last, the sales will be there.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
