<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wordpress on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/wordpress/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wordpress on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 15:48:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/wordpress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A peek under the hood of the website revamp</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/a-peek-under-the-hood-of-the-website-revamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 15:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/a-peek-under-the-hood-of-the-website-revamp/</guid>
      <description>
_Image by riversidetransportunder a CC-BY-NC-SA license</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog updates</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/blog-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 16:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/blog-updates/</guid>
      <description>I’m in the process of changing servers at my current host, and the last website I had to do was this one. Over the course of last weekend, I decided to finish it, and did a mysqldump of my WordPress database, in addition to updating to the latest version to avoid a security flaw. I about had a heart attack when I saw my database (not gzipped) was 3.3 gigabytes. Sure, I’ve been blogging for 5 years (more on that later this month), but 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovin&#39; Feedburner</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/05/lovin-feedburner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2007 22:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/05/lovin-feedburner/</guid>
      <description>About 6 months ago, I burned my blog’s RSS feed to Feedburner. I was using WP-Shortstat as a WordPress plugin, and the RSS feed subscribers didn’t look realistic (and they weren’t!) as it was over reporting on the number of subscribers. I’ve been happy with Feedburner since, and it provided a very simple view to my feed’s statistics, and there was a plugin to view the statistics right in my WordPress dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Updates</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/01/website-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2007 14:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/01/website-updates/</guid>
      <description>I updated the blog to WordPress 2.1 last night, which has a lots of little updates. The upgrade went perfectly, and my theme and plugins seem to work without any errors.
I finally found the option in WordPress to update the feed to full posts instead of the summaries, which makes the blog much more friendly to RSS readers. A bonus effect is that it fixes the Daily Links post to post in bullet summaries in feedreaders instead of mashing the post in to one paragraph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 2.0</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/12/wordpress-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2005 15:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/12/wordpress-20/</guid>
      <description>I’ve upgraded the ole blog to WordPress 2.0 and the K2 theme to the latest, revision 151.
Overall, I’m pretty impressed. Visually, it’s much better, though the post editor is now a more WYSIWYG type, and there seem to be some kinks to be worked out with that, but I’m guessing it may have to do with a Firefox extension I’m using. The plugins I use (FlickrRSS, Ultimate Tag Warrior) seem to work, and I’ve switched from Spam Karma 2 to Akismet for spam blockage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flock</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/10/flock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2005 00:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/10/flock/</guid>
      <description>I’ve downloaded Flock the new browser for Web 2.0 based on Firefox.
More to come – it’s very interesting but I don’t think I quite have the hang of it yet – though I am posting this blog post from Flock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spam Karma 2</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/10/spam-karma-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2005 11:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/10/spam-karma-2/</guid>
      <description>I continue to be impressed with Spam Karma 2 for WordPress since I installed in a couple weeks ago.
I was getting about 50 spam comments a day in the blog, and Spam Karma 2 has cut that down to nothing. Zero. Zilch. I think I’ve had to moderate 3 comments so far it wasn’t sure of (which were spam), but that’s nothing compared to the daily maintenance hell I used to go through in deleting comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Upgraded</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/09/theme-upgraded/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2005 02:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/09/theme-upgraded/</guid>
      <description>Upgraded to the latest and greatest K2 theme – and now comes with the Vader style. Back to a black theme, yay!
Even better, comes with AJAX commenting. Sweet.
Mike and Chris are writing some rockin’ code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Updated</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/09/wordpress-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2005 00:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/09/wordpress-updated/</guid>
      <description>A number of updates:
 Updated to WordPress 1.52 Updated the K2 theme to K2 Beta One r77 and then added the Burum Style Added the Spam Karma 2 plug-in to combat the massive amounts of comment spam I’ve been receiving lately Added the Flickr RSS plug-in instead of using a Flickr badge Added some more links on the right  Now on to upgrading Drupal to 4.6.3 over at Apatheia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Blog</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/09/ubuntu-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2005 11:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2005/09/ubuntu-blog/</guid>
      <description>I was taking a peek at WordPress.com (more on that in a minute) and it showed one of the top hosted blogs there is the Ubuntu weblog.
It already has some nice tips and tricks posted (like the bash command append). I’ll definitely be adding that to my blogroll.
WordPress.com is similar to Movable Type – hosted blog solution for users who don’t want or have a server to host their own blog on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
