<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kickstarter on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/kickstarter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kickstarter on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 16:25:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/kickstarter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Larry Elmore: The Complete Elmore Artbook</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/larry-elmore-the-complete-elmore-artbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 16:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/larry-elmore-the-complete-elmore-artbook/</guid>
      <description>If you played Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons in the 80s, read the Dragonlance novels published by TSR or played Everquest, chances are you have seen artwork by Larry Elmore.
Just about a year ago Mr. Elmore launched a Kickstarter to publish most of his painted art from the last 40 years, and it was successfully funded on New Year’s Eve of 2012.
Imagine my surprise yesterday when the US Postal Service rang my doorbell and delivered my Kickstarter package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kicking off a week about Kickstarter (and how I became a loyal Polyvinyl Records customer)</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/03/kicking-off-a-week-about-kickstarter-and-how-i-became-a-loyal-polyvinyl-records-customer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 13:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/03/kicking-off-a-week-about-kickstarter-and-how-i-became-a-loyal-polyvinyl-records-customer/</guid>
      <description>[http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/mattlunsford/help-us-save-our-office/widget/card.html]
You can’t turn around these days without hearing about Kickstarter. From movies, music, books or technology products, it seems everyone is using Kickstarter to raise funds to start a project. Over the course of the next week, I’ll be blogging about some of the projects I’ve backed, reviews, and thoughts about how Kickstarter may be used in the future.
What is Kickstarter? From their frequently asked questions:
 _Kickstarter is a funding platform for creative projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder MMO on Kickstarter</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/pathfinder-mmo-on-kickstarter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 16:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/pathfinder-mmo-on-kickstarter/</guid>
      <description>Photo by fireflythegreatunder a CC-BY 2.0 licenseJust before Christmas, I visited my local gaming store with the intent of buying the Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons Basic Set to play with the kids over the holiday break. It was time to step up from RPGKids, which I started with the kids a year or two ago. I’m a terrible Dungeon Master and lack creativity, so one of the things I was excited about in buying a set was that I’d be able to buy modules to help create the adventures for the kids.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
