<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 13:36:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The “Last” Science Fiction / Fantasy Meme</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/10/the-last-science-fiction-fantasy-meme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 13:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/10/the-last-science-fiction-fantasy-meme/</guid>
      <description>SF Signal, the most recent Hugo award winning fanzine, posted a meme on Saturday with a “last” theme. Here we go:
 The last sf/f book I finished reading: Shift Omnibus by Hugh Howey The last sf/f book I did NOT finish: Perdido Street Station by China Miéville (I loved The City &amp;amp; the City but just could not finish this one. It’s very rare for me to not finish a book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready Player One is the best book you’re not reading</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/08/ready-player-one-is-the-best-book-youre-not-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 13:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/08/ready-player-one-is-the-best-book-youre-not-reading/</guid>
      <description>If you grew up in the 80s like me, especially as a teenager, Ready Player One is a book for you.
For fans of retro arcade games, 80s music and movies, MMOs, cyberpunk, roleplaying and early computers like the TRS-80, it weaves them all into a story that will keep you on the edge of your seat.
I can’t do it justice, so read the summary here. And then buy it and read it, you won’t be disappointed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gregory Mcdonald, RIP</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/09/gregory-mcdonald-rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 13:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/09/gregory-mcdonald-rip/</guid>
      <description>Gregory Mcdonald, most famous for being the author of the Fletch series, has died at age 71 from cancer.
I’m not a big mystery reader, but due to Kevin Smith‘s praise for McDonald’s dialogue in his novels, I picked up one or two of his books, and then quickly bought them all a number of years ago.
You thought the Fletch movies (well, at least the first one) were funny? Each and every one of these books will have you chuckling and laughing out loud at some point, and the mysteries weren’t half bad either.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
