<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arcade on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/arcade/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Arcade on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 20:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/arcade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RetroPie Update</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/04/retropie-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/04/retropie-update/</guid>
      <description>I hooked up the Raspberry Pi to test it out. I did an update and it broke the boot up process and now wants the username and password. Think I remember that? Nope! Of course I don’t remember the password. So I downloaded a new RetroPie image which has led me down a rabbit hole of MAME configuration. The buttons on the controller don’t seem to be mapped correctly.
I did downloaded a new romset from the Internet Archive for MAME 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practice Cuts</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/04/practice-cuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/04/practice-cuts/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago I asked Kelly for help in drawing the arcade on the plywood. I had tried to draw the lines for the top of the cabinet, but I just couldn’t visualize it. (It’s both an ongoing joke and the truth that her spacial relationships are a hundred times better than mine. You don’t want to see me try to even pack a suitcase, I’m terrible). I also needed help with how to draw the curves along the sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Prep</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/04/video-prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/04/video-prep/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve spent this week watching some videos and preparing for today when I&amp;rsquo;m going to make a practice cut for the first time using the circular saw and jigsaw. The hardest part is figuring out the curve of the cut for the side panel. The Geek Pub FAQ says this is explained in the video for the mini bartop. I just watched that video - and it&amp;rsquo;s not explained at all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future Arcade Planning</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/03/future-arcade-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/03/future-arcade-planning/</guid>
      <description>Kelly and I talked about the arcade today. She told me something I had already thought to myself - that this probably won’t be the last arcade I build. I&amp;rsquo;m going to make mistakes and want to do it again. This came up in the context of doing the router work for the t-molding. She recommended I don’t do the t-molding on the first build as I’m going to make mistakes and will probably want to do it again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixelcade</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/03/pixelcade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/03/pixelcade/</guid>
      <description>I sold a bunch of my old Sonos equipment and decided to splurge on the arcade. I had been looking at GameOnGrafix for artwork for the side panels and the marquee for the arcade cabinet. I was undecided what I wanted to do as Kelly has a vinyl cutter, so it might be possible to make my own side panel art, but I was going to need a marquee.
And then I found the Pixelcade, which is an LED marquee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Control Panel Prototype Failures</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/03/more-control-panel-prototype-failures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/03/more-control-panel-prototype-failures/</guid>
      <description>Kelly needed to replace the blade in the saw and she cut me a new piece of wood to use as a prototype for the control panel. (At some point, I&amp;rsquo;m going to need to learn to use the saws!) After carefully paying attention to using the right size drill bit, my board looks like this:
Kelly then took a turn at doing it herself, and hers ended up the same way, so I don&amp;rsquo;t feel too bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Control Panel Prototypes</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/01/control-panel-prototypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/01/control-panel-prototypes/</guid>
      <description>If I don&amp;rsquo;t improve my attention to detail, I&amp;rsquo;m going to waste a lot of time and money. Case in point: just trying to build a prototype for the control panel so I can figure out how to use the Ipac controller and arcade buttons.
The first prototype I built 18 months ago I built upside down. I tried to fix it, but it was just uncomfortable to use.
The second control panel I drilled the holes the wrong size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting the Arcade Cabinet Again</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/01/starting-the-arcade-cabinet-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2020/01/starting-the-arcade-cabinet-again/</guid>
      <description>After a year and a half break from working on the arcade cabinet, it&amp;rsquo;s time to start again. I&amp;rsquo;ve started keeping a journal of my progress and I figured I might as well blog about it as well. I&amp;rsquo;ll use this to keep track of my progress, what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned, and post some photos, too.
I&amp;rsquo;ve never done any woodworking - or really used power tools before - so I have a lot to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
