<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bob mould on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/bob-mould/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bob mould on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2014 14:20:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/bob-mould/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I love Minnesota Music</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/09/i-love-minnesota-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2014 14:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/09/i-love-minnesota-music/</guid>
      <description>As a transplant to Minnesota from Wisconsin, I’ve now spent over half my life here. I’m a cheesehead through and through, but if there is one thing that Minnesota has that Wisconsin has never had, it’s the music. The first album I ever bought was Prince’s Purple Rain and my first ever trip to Minnesota I actually met Prince, which is another story for a different time. A few years later I was living here and I won tickets on Rev105 to a local music showcase at First Avenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorite Albums of 2012</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/favorite-albums-of-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 21:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/favorite-albums-of-2012/</guid>
      <description>With 2012 here and gone, I wanted to share my favorite albums of 2012. These aren’t necessarily the “best” albums of 2012, but these were the ones I enjoyed immensely over the past year. Almost every single one I bought on vinyl and streamed on Rdio. I tried to condense the list to a top 10, but I just couldn’t do it. I’m not going to do a major review of each one – there are plenty of sites out there from Paste to Pitchfork that can give you more information on the artists and albums below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I’m Listening to: New Music Releases 7/25</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2012/07/what-im-listening-to-new-music-releases-725/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 12:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2012/07/what-im-listening-to-new-music-releases-725/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back!
July 25th is a big day for new music. If you’re not reading the Largeheartedboy blog for new music releases, including where you can stream the new releases for free before buying (which usually comes out on Wednesdays), you should be. The list of today’s releases can be found here.
Albums I’ve purchased this week include:
Passion Pit’s Gossamer: If you’re a fan of the first album, you’ll love their second album.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roundup 6/17/11</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/06/roundup-61711/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 14:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/06/roundup-61711/</guid>
      <description>A few links to wrap up your week:
 Minneapolis legend Bob Mould stopped by 89.3 The Current at the UBS Forum this week and read from his new autobiography, See a Little Light, and performed a few songs which you can listen to at The Current. NPR reviews his new book as well. The Foo Fighters latest album, Wasting Light, is on sale today for only $3.99. Fantastic album, recorded on analog tape, and produced by Butch Vig who produced Nirvana’s Nevermind and he’s alo the founder of Garbage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
