<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>netflix on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/netflix/</link>
    <description>Recent content in netflix on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 16:08:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/netflix/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Six Months Without Satellite TV</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/six-months-without-satellite-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 16:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/six-months-without-satellite-tv/</guid>
      <description>It’s been six months since I cut the cable and canceled DirecTV, going over-the-air and internet only.
Do I miss DirecTV?
In a word, no.
This past Sunday started the real test as I’m a huge (American) football fan. Living in Minnesota and being a Green Bay Packers fan, this season is the first in ten years that I haven’t had DirecTV’s NFL Sunday ticket to watch out of market games (luckily the Packers were the national game this past Sunday).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cutting the cable</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/cutting-the-cable/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 22:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/cutting-the-cable/</guid>
      <description>I’m an entertainment junkie. I own hundreds of music CD’s, books, movies and am an early adopter of Blu-Ray. My usual routine once my two youngest children are in bed at 8 pm is to plop down on my couch, put my notebook on my lap and use that while watching my pretty 60″ TV.
I’ve received my TV content from DirecTV for the last ten years since we built this house – primarily because I’m a huge (American) football fan, and my team, the Green Bay Packers, are out of market where I live and DirecTV has a monopoly on the NFL package to be able to watch my team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/netflix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2008 01:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/netflix/</guid>
      <description>After a two year break, I signed up for Netflix again. Towards the end of my last subscription, I was paying $15 / month to hang on to two or three DVDs I never got around to watching. I’m the type of customer Netflix loves – really active, then a couple months of inactivity.
To curb my habit of buying Blu-Ray movies (they’re so pretty in HD!), I signed up again yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
