<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Movies on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/movies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Movies on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 12:53:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/movies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Achievement Unlocked: Geek Dad Cred</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/04/achievement-unlocked-geek-dad-cred/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 12:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/04/achievement-unlocked-geek-dad-cred/</guid>
      <description>I took the kids to Captain America: The Winter Soldier this past Sunday. You know it’s going to be a blockbuster when the theater is 75% filled at a 9:30 a.m. showing on a Sunday morning. I usually like to take the kids to the early showing as the theater is almost empty on Sunday mornings.
Warning: Minor Spoiler
Two thirds of the way through the movie, Natasha Romanova (Black Widow), played by Scarlett Johansson, and Steve Rogers (Captain America), played by Chris Evans, enter an abandoned military base with an ancient mainframe computer system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Things Blade Runner</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/11/all-things-blade-runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 13:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/11/all-things-blade-runner/</guid>
      <description>Over thirty years later, Blade Runner still remains one of my favorite films (as I’ve previously blogged about). It was only six weeks ago that I sat down and watched it again – it is easily one of the movies I can watch over and over and still enjoy with a sense of wonder.
I’m not the only one who shares a passion for Blade Runner, as fans have paid tribute to the classic film in a few ways in 2013:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audi’s latest commercial features a hilarious take on Old Spock vs. New Spock</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/05/audis-latest-commercial-features-a-hilarious-take-on-old-spock-vs-new-spock/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 19:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/05/audis-latest-commercial-features-a-hilarious-take-on-old-spock-vs-new-spock/</guid>
      <description>I have to hand it to Audi – this is the funniest commercial I’ve seen in some time, especially outside of the Super Bowl.
This commercial has it all – and the best part is some of the in-jokes for Star Trek fans. I don’t want to spoil it for you, so go spend 2 minutes of your life and watch it.
[http://www.youtube.com/embed/WPkByAkAdZs]
(via io9)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was REALLY behind the destruction of the Death Star?</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/03/who-was-really-behind-the-destruction-of-the-death-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 15:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/03/who-was-really-behind-the-destruction-of-the-death-star/</guid>
      <description>You decide.
[http://www.youtube.com/embed/2dvv-Yib1Xg]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cutting the Cable, Part 2</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/cutting-the-cable-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 21:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/cutting-the-cable-part-2/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago I blogged about buying the hardware to set up a MythTV PC to record off air high def TV and integrate it with Boxee.
The hardware arrived and I’ve been working on on the setup off and on over the last few weeks. Some random thoughts:
  The HD Homerun tuner is pretty cool. Fedora has the HD Homerun configuration tool in their repos. Installing that through PackageKit and yum made it easy to test out that it was working and had a good signal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cutting the cable</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/cutting-the-cable/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 22:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/01/cutting-the-cable/</guid>
      <description>I’m an entertainment junkie. I own hundreds of music CD’s, books, movies and am an early adopter of Blu-Ray. My usual routine once my two youngest children are in bed at 8 pm is to plop down on my couch, put my notebook on my lap and use that while watching my pretty 60″ TV.
I’ve received my TV content from DirecTV for the last ten years since we built this house – primarily because I’m a huge (American) football fan, and my team, the Green Bay Packers, are out of market where I live and DirecTV has a monopoly on the NFL package to be able to watch my team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eBook Readers &amp; the Publishing Industry</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/12/ebook-readers-the-publishing-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 15:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/12/ebook-readers-the-publishing-industry/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been wanting an eReader for a while. When the Kindle first launched, I was in awe. I quickly sat down and calculated the number of books I buy in a year and compared that against the cost of a Kindle and the savings of buying an e-book for $10 vs. the hardcover price. Let’s just say there wasn’t much of a savings. I finally got to touch a Kindle at GUADEC this summer, and my mind was made up that I had to have an eReader in the near future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/netflix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2008 01:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/netflix/</guid>
      <description>After a two year break, I signed up for Netflix again. Towards the end of my last subscription, I was paying $15 / month to hang on to two or three DVDs I never got around to watching. I’m the type of customer Netflix loves – really active, then a couple months of inactivity.
To curb my habit of buying Blu-Ray movies (they’re so pretty in HD!), I signed up again yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blu-Ray goes for the knockout blow</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/blu-ray-goes-for-the-knockout-blow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2008 01:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/blu-ray-goes-for-the-knockout-blow/</guid>
      <description>The news is everywhere: Warner, the last remaining major studio to support both high def video formats in HD-DVD and Blu-Ray has announced that as of May they will support Blu-Ray exclusively.
Toshiba, owner of the HD-DVD patent? Suprised. And even better, Warner, unlike Universal when they went HD-DVD exclusive, didn’t take a dime.
Even though both formats are burdened with DRM, I have to say I love my Blu-Ray player – it’s amazing the difference in HD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bladerunner:  The Final Cut</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/12/bladerunner-the-final-cut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2007 23:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/12/bladerunner-the-final-cut/</guid>
      <description>I headed to downtown Minneapolis Friday afternoon, and caught a screening of Bladerunner: The Final Cut.
It’s been 48 hours since I saw the film, and it touches me in a way few films do – I sit here and still struggle to put in to words the emotions Bladerunner evokes for me. From the themes of consumerism and humanism to the grim picture the film paints of the future, few science fiction films hold up as well as Bladerunner does after twenty-five years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
