<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 12:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Listening to my Record Collection Alphabetically</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2021/02/listening-to-my-record-collection-alphabetically/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/posts/2021/02/listening-to-my-record-collection-alphabetically/</guid>
      <description>I love this blog post from Discogs. I’ve often thought of doing exactly what it lays out: listen to your record collection from A to Z.
I know there are a lot of records I rarely listen to. Whether I bought them because I love the artist, because of their rarity, or just because I was taking a chance on something new, I’m sure there are records collecting dust.
I’ve done a pretty good job, especially last year in the first year of the pandemic, selling off any records I know I won’t listen to again on Discogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prince Rogers Nelson 1958 – 2016</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2016/04/prince/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 14:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2016/04/prince/</guid>
      <description>Prince has always held a special place for me. I spent my summers growing up with grandparents, an hour north of the suburbs of Milwaukee, where I lived. In 1984 I was 11 and I still remember walking to the record shop to purchase my first record, Prince’s Purple Rain. Years later, I would joke that if my grandparents or parents knew of some of the lyrics on that album, I would never have been able to buy it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I love Minnesota Music</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/09/i-love-minnesota-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2014 14:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/09/i-love-minnesota-music/</guid>
      <description>As a transplant to Minnesota from Wisconsin, I’ve now spent over half my life here. I’m a cheesehead through and through, but if there is one thing that Minnesota has that Wisconsin has never had, it’s the music. The first album I ever bought was Prince’s Purple Rain and my first ever trip to Minnesota I actually met Prince, which is another story for a different time. A few years later I was living here and I won tickets on Rev105 to a local music showcase at First Avenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Pages’ Oral History of 89.3 The Current</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/01/city-pages-oral-history-of-the-current/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 14:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/01/city-pages-oral-history-of-the-current/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago I was out watching football with some buddies. I was talking about my new car and how I was disappointed it didn’t have Radio Data System built in, which shows you the song name and title when listening to the radio. “Who still listens to the radio?!” he said. I replied, “I listen to The Current! We have one of the best public radio stations in the country!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorite Albums of 2013</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/01/favorite-albums-of-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 22:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/01/favorite-albums-of-2013/</guid>
      <description>[http://www.flickr.com/photos/silwenae/11061236153/in/set-72157638067918784/player/]
With 2013 now in the books, I’d like to share some of my favorite albums of 2013. After Polica dropped their debut album digitally on December 20th, 2011, I’ve learned to wait until the year is over to share my favorite albums – don’t want to miss one!
These might not be the critic’s choices, but these are albums I like, and almost all of them I’ve bought on vinyl this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best of Bootie 2013 Released!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/best-of-bootie-2013-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 19:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/best-of-bootie-2013-released/</guid>
      <description>Best of Bootie 2013 is out! And just in time for Christmas, too!
Featuring 22 of the year’s best mashups from some of the best DJs currently in the business, Best of Bootie 2013 is available as one big MP3 file or 22 tracks in one convenient zip file. Curated by A Plus D, aka DJs Adrian &amp;amp; Mysterious D, founders of Bootie, they didn’t just stop with their 22 favorite mashups – there are also 10 bonus mashups available for download, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon’s Frustration Free Packaging</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/amazons-frustration-free-packaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 00:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/amazons-frustration-free-packaging/</guid>
      <description>“Certified” to be frustration free. Especially when they tape over the easy open pull tab when you’re trying to get to your new shiny vinyl record.
(It’s Volcano Choir’s first album, Unmap, if you were curious.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August Vinyl</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/10/august-vinyl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 13:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/10/august-vinyl/</guid>
      <description>Summer is the slow time for new music releases and August saw a number of great new releases, with even more coming later this fall.
Here’s some of the new releases I picked up on vinyl in August:
 Superchunk – I Hate Music: The alt rockers have been around since 1989(!) and I Hate Music is their tenth album. The album is short and sweet, clocking in at just over 37 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chvrches – The Bones of What You Believe In</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/09/chvrches-the-bones-of-what-you-believe-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 13:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/09/chvrches-the-bones-of-what-you-believe-in/</guid>
      <description>One of the albums I’ve been looking forward to the most this year is finally out today. The Bones of What You Believe In by the Glasgow band Chvrches has had singles released all summer long and the wait has been killing me. I’m only half way through my first listen on Rdio and it’s everything I wanted and more.
UPS will be delivering my vinyl copy later today and I can’t wait to give it a spin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pearl Jam – Mind Your Manners</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/07/pearl-jam-mind-your-manners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 12:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/07/pearl-jam-mind-your-manners/</guid>
      <description>Pearl Jam is back with a new single from their upcoming 10th release, Lightning Bolt.
Check out “Mind Your Manners” – a punk inspired, hard rocker. Can’t wait!
 [//www.youtube.com/embed/DhODYyZVL6Y]</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
