<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Games on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Games on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 13:15:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Dungeons &amp; Dragons Matters</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/01/why-dungeons-dragons-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 13:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/01/why-dungeons-dragons-matters/</guid>
      <description>40 years of using your imagination. Ethan Gilsdorf has a fantastic essay up on Boing Boing: At 40 Years Old, Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons Still Matters. As the original Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons turns 40 this year, I’m guessing we’ll see many great tributes to the grandaddy of all role playing games, and Mr. Gilsdorf’s essay really resonated with me.
 Along the way, D&amp;amp;Ders like me learned about stuff. We discussed hit dice and saving throws, ballistas and halberds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gearbox wins Homeworld Auction</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/10/gearbox-wins-homeworld-auction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 13:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/10/gearbox-wins-homeworld-auction/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Johnny Wallker under a CC-NC-ND 2.0 license I’m cleaning up some open tabs and a story of interest to me is related to the 1999 game Homeworld from Relic Entertainment.
Relic Entertainment was bought by THQ in 2004 and THQ went bankrupt this year, auctioning off a lot of old assets, Homeworld included. Six months ago TeamPixel, a small studio, started a Kickstarter campaign to gather support to try and win the rights to Homeworld from the bankruptcy court.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neil Gaiman introduces his first game, Wayward Manor</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/07/neil-gaiman-introduces-his-first-game-wayward-manor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 13:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/07/neil-gaiman-introduces-his-first-game-wayward-manor/</guid>
      <description>For the last few weeks, Neil Gaiman has tweeted links to a cryptic new website that asked you to RSVP (via email) to a website, Who Haunts Neil. Yesterday, if you had sent an RSVP, you received an email with an update to this very mysterious site, with Mr. Gaiman hosting a video introducing his latest project: Wayward Manor.
Neil, in partnership with game studio The Odd Gentlemen, is launching his first game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My OUYA came!</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/05/my-ouya-came/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 12:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/05/my-ouya-came/</guid>
      <description>My OUYA came! Thoughts coming soon….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support Small World on Kickstarter (Especially for Table Top Day!)</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/03/support-small-world-on-kickstarter-especially-for-table-top-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 14:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/03/support-small-world-on-kickstarter-especially-for-table-top-day/</guid>
      <description>[http://www.youtube.com/embed/x3m0PIWqkfQ]
This Saturday, March 30th, is Table Top Day! Geek &amp;amp; Sundry has organized an international day to support, enjoy and play table top games. About a year ago a friend invited a friend of ours, my eldest son and myself over to have a table top gaming night. I was blown away by number of games now available. You’ve probably heard of some of the biggest, such as Settlers of Catan, but there is a revolution going on in old school games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can arcades make a comeback?</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/02/can-arcades-make-a-comeback/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 17:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/02/can-arcades-make-a-comeback/</guid>
      <description>Having been born in the early 70’s, I am a child of the 80’s. One of the best parts of being a child of the 80’s was living through the boom (and later bust) of the arcades. Whether it was going to Godfather’s Pizza and playing a handful of arcade games or Chuck E. Cheese with dozens of games or getting dropped off at an arcade in a mall while my parents went shopping, the fun in plugging quarters in for hours can never be re-lived.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder MMO on Kickstarter</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/pathfinder-mmo-on-kickstarter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 16:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/pathfinder-mmo-on-kickstarter/</guid>
      <description>Photo by fireflythegreatunder a CC-BY 2.0 licenseJust before Christmas, I visited my local gaming store with the intent of buying the Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons Basic Set to play with the kids over the holiday break. It was time to step up from RPGKids, which I started with the kids a year or two ago. I’m a terrible Dungeon Master and lack creativity, so one of the things I was excited about in buying a set was that I’d be able to buy modules to help create the adventures for the kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portal 2</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/portal-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 16:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/portal-2/</guid>
      <description>Playing Portal 2 for the first time with Zoe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rpgKids</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/10/rpgkids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 13:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/10/rpgkids/</guid>
      <description>A co-worker introduced me to rpgKids last week. After taking a look around the website, I plunked down the $5 and bought the game and the adventure pack and it was well worth the money.
rpgKids is a basic roleplaying game meant to introduce kids ages 4-7 to the wonderful world of using their imagination to roleplay. The 24 page PDF includes the ruleset, an overview of the characters, hand drawn tokens for both heroes and monsters, a character sheet and a printable 1″ grid for mapping your adventures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family D&amp;D</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/03/family-dd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 20:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/03/family-dd/</guid>
      <description>Wil Wheaton is blogging about something I’ve always wanted to do, which is to run a D&amp;amp;D campaign for his son. (Part 1, Part 2, Part 3, Part 4, and Part 5).
I even went so far as a couple of years ago in buying the 3rd edition Players Handbook, DM Guide and Monster Manual, but I never did run a campaign.
Why not?
I suck as a DM.
I’m just not creative or flexible enough that when a player throws me for a curve to react.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
