<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>&amp;quot;Talk Python&amp;quot; on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/quottalk-pythonquot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in &amp;quot;Talk Python&amp;quot; on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 12:57:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/quottalk-pythonquot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Python for Entrepeneurs Progress</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2017/07/python-for-entrepeneurs-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 12:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2017/07/python-for-entrepeneurs-progress/</guid>
      <description>I sat down excited at dinner last night excited to share with my wife the two things I learned in my Talk Python course yesterday. The first was learning the basics of CSS, something I’ve avoided for years. I’m not going to even pretend I understand CSS, but it’s a base knowledge to work with and there is still a whole chapter of applied front-end frameworks, so I’m sure there will be more on CSS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talk Python Training: Consuming HTTP Services in Python Review</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2017/02/talk-python-training-consuming-http-services-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 17:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2017/02/talk-python-training-consuming-http-services-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Summary / tl;dr: Consuming HTTP Services in Python is a great addition to the training courses from Talk Python and Michael Kennedy. You’ll come away with a thorough knowledge of the best way to get data from the internet using the requests module; you’ll use real world examples and APIs from Basecamp, Github and a custom API Michael built just from the course; Michael will explain and show the concepts in an easy to learn manner with a little humor and recap each concept to make sure you understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Year of Python</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2016/12/one-year-of-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 16:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2016/12/one-year-of-python/</guid>
      <description>It was Black Friday of 2015. O’Reilly put on a sale of their programming ebooks and I was finally ready to take the plunge and learn Python. I bought three books:
 Learning Python 5th edition by Mark Lutz Python Pocket Reference by Mark Lutz Think Python 2nd edition by Allen B. Downey  I then signed up for a Coursera class, Python for Everybody, taught by Dr. Charles Severance and started the class.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
