<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 12:36:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rebooting my productivity without technology</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2016/03/rebooting-my-productivity-without-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 12:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2016/03/rebooting-my-productivity-without-technology/</guid>
      <description>Early last year I ran to Target on a Sunday morning on the spur of the moment. I wanted a Moleskin notebook, the small one that fits in your back pocket.
I wanted to get in a habit of writing down everything, especially ideas for writing prompts.
That lasted about a week for me. This is typical for me, especially when I try to create a new habit impulsively.
For the last couple of years, I’ve also been a huge fan of Wunderlist as a to-do application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cherry Tree Blooming in Kyoto, Japan</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/04/cherry-tree-blooming-in-kyoto-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 13:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/04/cherry-tree-blooming-in-kyoto-japan/</guid>
      <description>Winter never ends. I just returned home from 10 days in Asia, with a weekend stopover in Japan, staying in Osaka with a day trip to Kyoto.
It’s cold, snowing and blustery in Minneapolis on April 1st, so here’s a photo of a cherry tree just starting to blossom in Kyoto, Japan. We were a week or two early to enjoy the full cherry trees coming in to blossom, but there were a few just starting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombies don’t have a chance versus Nature</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/10/zombies-dont-have-a-chance-versus-nature/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 07:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/10/zombies-dont-have-a-chance-versus-nature/</guid>
      <description>We all love zombies. The Walking Dead is one of the most popular TV shows currently on. A new zombie movie seems to come out every year.
But a real zombie apocalypse? Nature would never let it happen.
BoingBoing has a great essay up by National Wildlife Federation naturalist David Mizejewski on how nature would deal with a zombie outbreak. From birds to mammals to bacteria, zombies wouldn’t stand a chance:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year and welcome back</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/happy-new-year-and-welcome-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 14:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/01/happy-new-year-and-welcome-back/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the revamped paulcutler.org.
I’m your host, Paul. With January upon us, the blog has officially turned 10(!). One of my New Years resolutions is to blog more – I only blogged twice last year, but I can’t tell you the number of ideas I had for blog posts that I saved in Evernote, Google Reader or Pocket / Instapaper. This year I hope to follow through on that a bit more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going to see Wits</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/06/going-to-see-wits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 15:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/06/going-to-see-wits/</guid>
      <description>This Friday, my son and I are going to the Fitzgerald Theater in St. Paul to see the season finale of Minnesota Public Radio’s Wits series. Each performance features an interview with a cultural icon, a musical guest and other guests. I purchased tickets for this one specifically because of the featured guest: Neil Gaiman. Mr. Gaiman is touring in support of the tenth anniversary of his first novel, the class American Gods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On to greener pastures</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/05/on-to-greener-pastures/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 14:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/05/on-to-greener-pastures/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was my last day at Novell. I enjoyed the 1+ year I spent working there – helping to ship SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop to millions of end users through OEM partnerships was a fulfilling experience in knowing it helped Linux on the desktop grow.
To those of you I worked with and didn’t get a chance to say goodbye to yesterday, it was a pleasure working with you.
If anyone is looking for a product management / business development professional with open source experience, let me know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s get back at it</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/03/lets-get-back-at-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 14:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2011/03/lets-get-back-at-it/</guid>
      <description>After over two months(!) away (bad blogger!), I’m ready to get back at it.
Expect some music reviews, both of new and old albums, Record Store updates, and more.
Now on with the news…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock and Roll Hall of Fame Nominees Announced</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/rock-and-roll-hall-of-fame-nominees-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2010 15:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/rock-and-roll-hall-of-fame-nominees-announced/</guid>
      <description>The Rock and Roll Hall of Fame nominees have been announced for 2011. While there are a few good nominees, including the Beastie Boys, Neil Diamond and Tom Waits, there are the not so good. That list would include Bon Jovi, the J. Geils Band and Donna Summer. While each of them have contributed to the history of rock &amp;amp; roll, let’s put them in perspective of some of the groups and artists snubbed by the Hall of Fame:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get notified about new releases</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/get-notified-about-new-releases/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 20:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/09/get-notified-about-new-releases/</guid>
      <description>Albumreminder.com is a website that can automatically inform you of when your favorite artist has a new album coming out.
After signing up for an account, Albumreminder.com can import a list of your favorite artists from Last.fm or iTunes. You can then choose to be emailed the day of release or a few days before when your favorite artist has a new release coming out. Alternatively, you can turn off email notifications and subscribe to a personal RSS thread instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Vinyl (R)evolution</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/07/welcome-to-vinyl-revolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 23:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/07/welcome-to-vinyl-revolution/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Vinyl (R)Evolution – where I talk about the music I love. I can guarantee that my tastes are not your tastes but I’m confident you’ll find a story now and then that you can relate to.
I grew up listening to my parents music, which included artists such as ABBA, Billy Joel, Elton John and Cat Stevens. I hit my teenage years in the mid to late 80s and I started getting into 80s pop music, some hair metal bands, and hard rock before finally getting into grunge in the 90s and staying with that as it morphed into alternative and indie rock.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
