<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ubuntu on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/categories/ubuntu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ubuntu on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 May 2009 21:16:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/categories/ubuntu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu One</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/05/ubuntu-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2009 21:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/05/ubuntu-one/</guid>
      <description>I haven’t used Ubuntu in over two and a half years, but I’ve been watching the debate raging with the launch of Ubuntu One last week with interest.
In my opinion, the best commentary on the matter so far has been by Jim Campbell, an Ubuntu member, on his blog. I encourage you to read his take on it, and also the second comment posted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amusing</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/03/amusing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 13:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/03/amusing/</guid>
      <description>This may only amuse me, but the number of searches on my blog for “ubuntu banshee 0.98.2” has skyrocketed in the last day or two since Banshee’s recent release.
Just another reason to use Foresight! Conary’s ability to write a recipe to create a package is easier than almost every distribution out there. This gives us the ability not only to add packages quickly, but to maintain Foresight as a rolling distribution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Look Back at 2007</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/a-look-back-at-2007/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 18:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2008/01/a-look-back-at-2007/</guid>
      <description>One of my New Year’s Resolutions this year was to get more involved with GNOME and / or Ubuntu when the year started. Having used Ubuntu since it was first released, and Linux and GNOME specifically since 1999, I really wanted to give something back. After being utterly confused on where to even start with Ubuntu due to the number of volunteers and convoluted processes, I decided to start with GNOME.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Feather in Conary&#39;s Hat</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/07/a-feather-in-conarys-hat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2007 12:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/07/a-feather-in-conarys-hat/</guid>
      <description>Reading the article “Mepis to switch from Ubuntu to Debian” one thing jumped out at me:
 Woodford explained that Ubuntu is rebuilt almost from scratch every six months using source packages from Debian EXPERIMENTAL.
 In using Ubuntu for almost 3 years, that was my experience as well. I formatted and installed fresh more than I just did a apt-get dist-upgrade.
And that is one of the major features of Conary – managing your applications and dependencies so you should never have to “install fresh”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foresight Linux</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/03/foresight-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2007 03:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/03/foresight-linux/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned in my last post, I installed Foresight Linux on my second box last week. (Don’t worry Ubuntu fans, I’m still running Feisty on my main machine). To set expectations, this post is part mini-review of Foresight, part comparison to Ubuntu, and just my opinions and thoughts on Foresight after using another distribution for almost 3 years.
Foresight’s website and IRC channel sum up Foresight well:
 Foresight Linux is a Distribution which showcases some of the latest and greatest from GNOME.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteering leads me to Foresight Linux</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/03/volunteering-leads-me-to-foresight-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2007 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/03/volunteering-leads-me-to-foresight-linux/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been trying to spend some time giving back to projects I believe in. I spent a weekend reading through Ubuntu wiki pages on everything from setting up a LoCo, to helping the documentation team, becoming an Ubuntu member, and a lot more. After being a little overwhelmed by some of Ubuntu’s processes (and I do understand why they have them considering the sheer number of users and folks involved), I volunteered to help write some copy for the new gnome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banshee, Mugshot, and AWN</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/03/banshee-mugshot-and-awn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2007 22:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/03/banshee-mugshot-and-awn/</guid>
      <description>I was pleasantly suprised to see that Banshee is now supported by Mugshot. I’ve been running Feisty for the last few weeks, and haven’t found a Mugshot .deb yet, but on my second machine I was testing out Foresight (different story for later), which had an up to date package for Mugshot. I was playing music on my main PC, look over to my second PC with Mugshot, and it’s reporting what songs I’ve just played.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avant Window Navigator on Feisty Fawn Howto</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/02/avant-window-navigator-on-feisty-fawn-howto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2007 17:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/02/avant-window-navigator-on-feisty-fawn-howto/</guid>
      <description>With some help from Pveith on the Ubuntu Forums, I was able to compile Avant Window Navigator from Subversion. Per Pveith’s recommendation, I used checkinstall, which created a .deb for installation. I am running Beryl and an Nvidia graphics card. I added a Feisty Fawn Howto on the AWN wiki, here is how I got it working:
Step 1: Prepare your system
 sudo apt-get install checkinstall build-essential subversion  Step 2: Download the required dependencies</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Feisty Fawn Herd 4 Random Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/02/ubuntu-feisty-fawn-herd-4-random-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2007 17:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/02/ubuntu-feisty-fawn-herd-4-random-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>I took the plunge and installed Feisty Fawn Herd 4 on my main machine last night. Doing a dist-upgrade resulted in kernel panic when GRUB tried to load, so I threw in the Herd 4 CD, and did a clean install. (I know, I should be installing alpha software on my main machine, but it’s running so smooth so far…)
If you haven’t checked out Feisty Fawn yet, check out the wiki pages on Ubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love &amp; Hate Relationship</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/02/love-hate-relationship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2007 02:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2007/02/love-hate-relationship/</guid>
      <description>I love Linux – last month was my 8 year anniversary of using Linux in some form, and next month will be the 2 year anniversary of using Linux as my only operating system when I retired from gaming.
I love Ubuntu – I love the community, the developers committed to making Linux (and Debian) better (and easier), and the wealth of applications.
But some things drive me crazy about Linux, and today’s rant is about trying to get my microphone jack to work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
