<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dungeons &amp;amp; dragons on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/dungeons-amp-dragons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dungeons &amp;amp; dragons on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 13:15:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/dungeons-amp-dragons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Dungeons &amp; Dragons Matters</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/01/why-dungeons-dragons-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 13:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/01/why-dungeons-dragons-matters/</guid>
      <description>40 years of using your imagination. Ethan Gilsdorf has a fantastic essay up on Boing Boing: At 40 Years Old, Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons Still Matters. As the original Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons turns 40 this year, I’m guessing we’ll see many great tributes to the grandaddy of all role playing games, and Mr. Gilsdorf’s essay really resonated with me.
 Along the way, D&amp;amp;Ders like me learned about stuff. We discussed hit dice and saving throws, ballistas and halberds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Larry Elmore: The Complete Elmore Artbook</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/larry-elmore-the-complete-elmore-artbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 16:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2013/12/larry-elmore-the-complete-elmore-artbook/</guid>
      <description>If you played Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons in the 80s, read the Dragonlance novels published by TSR or played Everquest, chances are you have seen artwork by Larry Elmore.
Just about a year ago Mr. Elmore launched a Kickstarter to publish most of his painted art from the last 40 years, and it was successfully funded on New Year’s Eve of 2012.
Imagine my surprise yesterday when the US Postal Service rang my doorbell and delivered my Kickstarter package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family D&amp;D</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/03/family-dd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 20:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2009/03/family-dd/</guid>
      <description>Wil Wheaton is blogging about something I’ve always wanted to do, which is to run a D&amp;amp;D campaign for his son. (Part 1, Part 2, Part 3, Part 4, and Part 5).
I even went so far as a couple of years ago in buying the 3rd edition Players Handbook, DM Guide and Monster Manual, but I never did run a campaign.
Why not?
I suck as a DM.
I’m just not creative or flexible enough that when a player throws me for a curve to react.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
