<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Badgers on Paul Cutler</title>
    <link>https://paulcutler.org/tags/badgers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Badgers on Paul Cutler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul Cutler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2014 15:50:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulcutler.org/tags/badgers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>If Only I Could</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/06/if-only-i-could/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2014 15:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/06/if-only-i-could/</guid>
      <description>If only I could buy season tickets and follow the process, including the step my wife added for me. Some day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations Wisconsin Men’s Basketball</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/03/congrats-uwmbb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 14:36:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2014/03/congrats-uwmbb/</guid>
      <description>Congratulations to the University of Wisconsin’s Men’s Basketball team on their victory over Arizona to win the West Regional bracket and advance to the Final Four.
Tom Oates of the Wisconsin State Journal has an excellent article on what this means for Coach Bo Ryan.
The game was a nail biter, with the last 18 minutes of regulation being a one possession game before finally going into overtime and the Badgers pulling out a huge win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I have seen the future of TV</title>
      <link>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/11/i-have-seen-the-future-of-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 21:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulcutler.org/blog/2010/11/i-have-seen-the-future-of-tv/</guid>
      <description>…and it is the ESPN app on the new Xbox 360 update that was released today.
I’ve been in the beta for the new Xbox 360 dashboard for the last month or so, and with its release today, the embargo on blogging about it has been lifted.
Since I cut the cord and got rid of cable TV last February, the one thing that has been missing is sports. I’ve been tied to whatever the four major networks want to shovel at me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
